<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<groups>
  <group>
    <title>Transgender Resources and Education X-travaganza! (T*REX)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://facebook.com/evergreentrex">http://facebook.com/evergreentrex</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tesc.t.rex@gmail.com">tesc.t.rex@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The mission of T*REX is to provide resources, outreach, education, support, and advocacy for gender non-conforming students and allies.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of T*REX is to provide resources, outreach, education, support, and advocacy for gender non-conforming students and allies.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>
</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Vanishing Point Literary Magazine</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://vanishingpointlitmag.wordpress.com/">http://vanishingpointlitmag.wordpress.com/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tesc.vanishingpoint@gmail.com">tesc.vanishingpoint@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Vanishing Point is an arts and literary magazine for the students and faculty of The Evergreen State College.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Vanishing Point is an arts and literary magazine for the students and faculty of The Evergreen State College. We aim to represent a range of talent and styles while creating an atmosphere of openness and accessibility to both our readership and the artists who submit their work. We function as a gathering point for creative people in the form of a website and print publication.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>WashPIRG - Evergreen Chapter</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/WashPIRGatEvergreen">https://www.facebook.com/WashPIRGatEvergreen</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://washpirgevergreen.weebly.com">http://washpirgevergreen.weebly.com</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:washpirgevergreen@gmail.com">washpirgevergreen@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>WashPIRG aims to promote an ethic of civic responsibility by actively engaging students in a broad range of social issues through a program of civic engagement, public interest research and advocac</p></teaser>
    <content><p>WashPIRG aims to promote an ethic of civic responsibility by actively engaging students in a broad range of social issues through a program of civic engagement, public interest research and advocacy.</p>
<p>Weekly meetings Wednesdays from 5:00pm-6:00pm in SEM 2 D3105.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 D3105</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Way of Tea</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/500492533337311/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/500492533337311/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenchanoyu@gmail.com">evergreenchanoyu@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The purpose of the Way of Tea club is to enjoy and celebrate traditional Japanese tea culture.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The purpose of the Way of Tea club is to enjoy and celebrate traditional Japanese tea culture. We seek to provide a mindful space to momentarily abandon worldly problems and enjoy the simple pleasures of good company and tea.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 E3105</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Mondays 4:00-6:00pm </meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>W.O.L.F. (Wild Order for Living Free)</title>
    <teaser><p>By learning, sharing and teaching wilderness survival skills we, the Wild Order for Living Free, will help to create more self-reliant, empowered and environmentally aware individuals and communiti</p></teaser>
    <content><p>By learning, sharing and teaching wilderness survival skills we, the Wild Order for Living Free, will help to create more self-reliant, empowered and environmentally aware individuals and communities. We believe that the gifts of the natural world should be used with respect and reciprocity, in order to preserve the vitality of the wilderness and conserve its resources. Through the basics of wilderness survival, people can better learn to live within the ecological boundaries of our only home, Planet Earth.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Women of Color Coalition (WOCC)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Womyn-of-Color-Coalition-at-TESC-187161874653630/">https://www.facebook.com/Womyn-of-Color-Coalition-at-TESC-187161874653630/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenwocc@gmail.com">evergreenwocc@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The purpose of the Women of Color Coalition (WOCC) is to create community enrichment through events, conferences, activities, and spaces for women of color and their allies who are interested in eq</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The purpose of the Women of Color Coalition (WOCC) is to create community enrichment through events, conferences, activities, and spaces for women of color and their allies who are interested in equitable relationship building. Our intention is to develop an environment that allows for us to come together in solidarity and empower one another through cultural, educational and entertaining meetings and events. We aim to be a resource for students who want to explore identity and create visibility for women of color in our community, and provide personal time as well as exploring written work by women of color and creating workshops. We strive to utilize WOCC to educate and empower our members in honoring unique experiences, common ground, and celebrating cultural ties to support each other while navigating our campus community. All womyn welcome--QTPOC safe space.</p>
<p>Our office is located in the CAB building upstairs with Student Activities. Our office is for you to utilize. Computer, paints, radical books and zines. Just a safe space for us to chill on campus and organize in community.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>ReCAP</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/tesc.wrc">http://www.facebook.com/tesc.wrc</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tescwrc@gmail.com">tescwrc@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The mission of ReCAP (formally the Women's Resource Center) is to promote and advocate for gender equity and social justice on campus and in the larger community.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of ReCAP (formally the Women&#039;s Resource Center) is to promote and advocate for gender equity and social justice on campus and in the larger community. Our office strives to be a safe place to get information and connect with campus and community services. We provide free menstrual supplies, safe sex supplies, pregnancy tests, educational resources, and reading material for check-out.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM2 A2109</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays at 2:30-4:00pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Wonder Collective</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/wondercollective.evergreen">https://www.facebook.com/wondercollective.evergreen</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:wondercollective@gmail.com">wondercollective@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Wonder Collective aspires to inspire creative exploration through studio-based community and events which encourage spiritual growth through creative practices.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Wonder Collective aspires to inspire creative exploration through studio-based community and events which encourage spiritual growth through creative practices. The Wonder Collective&#039;s focus is adaptable to the membership. This year, the Wonder Collective is holding a weekly clay club and other ceramics-related programming.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Young Roots</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:youngroots@goodgrub.org">youngroots@goodgrub.org</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>To inspire the next generation to fall in love with their food, connect with their community, and with nature.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>To inspire the next generation to fall in love with their food, connect with their community, and with nature. Young Roots wants to create a safe place for nature-based activities that are educational, engaging, and fun. We want to increase community engagement by creating a structure that supports their growth-both as gardeners and as leaders within their families and communities. Young Roots organizes workshops that emphasize stewardship of the land, gardening practices, and the importance of local food systems. Young Roots aims to form a strong and supportive community of gardeners in which all learn, teach, and grow together. The group also strives to strengthen the bonds between Evergreen, GRuB, families of the surrounding community, and to instill the love of organic gardening in new gardeners, which will last a lifetime.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Movimiento Estudiantil Xican@ de Aztlan (MEXA)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/MEXAdeEvergreen">https://www.facebook.com/MEXAdeEvergreen</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Movimento Estudiantil Xican@ de Aztlan (MEXA) is a student organization that promotes higher education, cultura, and historia.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Movimento Estudiantil Xican@ de Aztlan (MEXA) is a student organization that promotes higher education, cultura, and historia. MEXA de Evergreen strives to expand the definition of Xicanismo to encompass the struggle of everyone who relates to our cause. MEXA was founded on the principles of self-determination for the liberation of our people</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>CAB 313</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays, 1:30pm - 3:30pm at the &quot;Front Table&quot; in the Student Activities office</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Native Student Alliance</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/nativestudentalliance.tesc">http://www.facebook.com/nativestudentalliance.tesc</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreen.nsa@gmail.com">evergreen.nsa@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Native Student Alliance (NSA) is committed to building positive relationships between Native and non-Native communities by hosting cultural events.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Native Student Alliance (NSA) is committed to building positive relationships between Native and non-Native communities by hosting cultural events. NSA is an inter-tribal organization that brings awareness to Indigenous issues in and outside of the Evergreen community. We strive to support our members and promote a welcoming community environment that respects our varying backgrounds while encouraging our efforts in social activism.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Natural History Club</title>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen State College Natural History Club functions to support individuals passionate about the Natural world.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen State College Natural History Club functions to support individuals passionate about the Natural world. We seek to create links with the broader Natural History community around topics ranging from natural history collections curation to field studies. We wish to bring related studies together to inspire discovery, curiosity, and responsibility in the natural sciences.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Non Traditional x2</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/evergreenNTx2">https://www.facebook.com/evergreenNTx2</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Evening &amp; Weekend and Non-Traditional students are often responsible for holding many worlds together at work, home, community, and school.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Evening &amp; Weekend and Non-Traditional students are often responsible for holding many worlds together at work, home, community, and school. How can we better support and recognize these dedicated students? NTx2 seeks to provide a community for students that are balancing many roles and responsibilities.Through networking, resource sharing, and advocacy we will strive to ensure that Evergreen supports the needs of every student on campus, including working students, returning students, and students with families.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Aquaponics Club</title>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Aquaponics Club aims to further the education, advancement, and application of aquaponics food production at The Evergreen State College.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Aquaponics Club aims to further the education, advancement, and application of aquaponics food production at The Evergreen State College. Through hands on learning, workshop and seminar, and community participation, the Evergreen Aquaponics Club will forward the renewable agriculture movement on campus and in the wider field.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Police Awareness and Student Safety (PASS)</title>
    <teaser><p>We seek to foster and build a safe, healthy, non-hostile environment on campus by working with students, administration, faculty, staff, community, and emergency responders at The Evergreen State C</p></teaser>
    <content><p>We seek to foster and build a safe, healthy, non-hostile environment on campus by working with students, administration, faculty, staff, community, and emergency responders at The Evergreen State College to increase the level of education and self-awareness and facilitate a dialogue about relevant issues.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Project S.O.L.</title>
    <teaser><p>As an organization which will keep community education and cooperation as our primary goals, Synthesize Our Lives (S.O.L.) will provide an expansive resource to students who would like to learn and</p></teaser>
    <content><p>As an organization which will keep community education and cooperation as our primary goals, Synthesize Our Lives (S.O.L.) will provide an expansive resource to students who would like to learn and share their knowledge of music production and dj-ing. Our group structure will resemble that of a cooperative in which all members will learn from presentations and workshlops on how to skillfully make and present music. Members will have the opportunity to volunteer to share their own knowledge and techniques as well.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Queer &amp; Trans People of Color (QTPOC)</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:qpocatevergreen@gmail.com">qpocatevergreen@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Queer &amp; Trans People of Color work to create a space for people who align with a QTPOC identity to come together and build community.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Queer &amp; Trans People of Color work to create a space for people who align with a QTPOC identity to come together and build community. We do so through holding space to dialogue &amp; process about topics that affect our community. We strive to create visibility for ourselves.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Riot to Follow Theater Productions</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/riottofollowtheaterproductions">https://www.facebook.com/riottofollowtheaterproductions</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://www.riottofollow.com">http://www.riottofollow.com</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:rtftheaterproductions@gmail.com">rtftheaterproductions@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Riot to Follow aims to provide an inclusive, professional, and student driven theater experience for everyone on our campus.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Riot to Follow aims to provide an inclusive, professional, and student driven theater experience for everyone on our campus. We provide opportunities for students from all majors and experience levels. We aim to make all of our shows free for students and the surrounding Olympia community, so as to be better able to spread and celebrate theater!</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>S&amp;A Board</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://evergreen.edu/activities/saboard">http://evergreen.edu/activities/saboard</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/EvergreenSABoard">https://www.facebook.com/EvergreenSABoard</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:saboard@evergreen.edu">saboard@evergreen.edu</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The S&amp;A Board is the student committee that allocates Services and Activities fees to all of the organizations you see here.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The S&amp;A Board is the student committee that allocates Services and Activities fees to all of the organizations you see here. This student committee renews itself annually and seeks new members every Fall.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>CAB 301</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Mondays &amp; Wednesdays 3-5 pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories>Governance</categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Socialist Alternative</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://www.socialistalternative.org">http://www.socialistalternative.org</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreensocialistalternative@gmail.com">evergreensocialistalternative@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We are a national organization fighting in our workplaces, communities, and campuses against the exploitation and injustices people face every day.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>We are a national organization fighting in our workplaces, communities, and campuses against the exploitation and injustices people face every day. We are community activists fighting against budget cuts in public services; we are activists campaigning for a $15/hour minimum wage and fighting, democratic unions; we are people of all colors speaking out against racism and attacks on immigrants, students organizing against tuition hikes and war, women and men fighting sexism and homophobia.</p>
<p>We believe the Republicans and Democrats are both parties of big business, and we are campaigning to build an independent, alternative party of workers and young people to fight for the interests of the millions, not the millionaires.</p>
<p>We see the global capitalist system as the root cause of the economic crisis, poverty, discrimination, war, and environmental destruction. As capitalism moves deeper into crisis, a new generation of workers and youth must join together to take the top 500 corporations into public ownership under democratic control to end the ruling elites’ global competition for profits and power.</p>
<p>We believe the dictatorships that existed in the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe were perversions of what socialism is really about. We are for democratic socialism where ordinary people will have control over our daily lives.</p>
<p>Socialist Alternative is also in political solidarity with the Committee for a Workers’ International, a worldwide socialist organization in 47 countries, on every continent. Join us!</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Society of Creative Costuming</title>
    <teaser><p>The Society of Creative Costuming aims to provide a space for all students to enthuse about, learn, and share their knowledge of costumes and the process behind making them.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Society of Creative Costuming aims to provide a space for all students to enthuse about, learn, and share their knowledge of costumes and the process behind making them. We will have various events throughout the school year to teach and learn about costumes and what makes them. All students with a passion for any aspects of costuming are welcome to join us, regardless of skill level or costuming background.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Student Art Gallery</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/EvergreenSAG">https://www.facebook.com/EvergreenSAG</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreensag@gmail.com">evergreensag@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Student Art Gallery is a network of students striving to provide support, community, and education for students interested in observing, creating, submitting, and/or curating art.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Student Art Gallery is a network of students striving to provide support, community, and education for students interested in observing, creating, submitting, and/or curating art. Art of all mediums and levels are welcome. We provide workshops, lectures and resources for the campus as well as regular shows and gallery hours. In addition to exhibiting their work, we provide training and experience curating, promoting, installing, and documenting student artwork.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Students for a Democratic Society (SDS)</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:olympiasds@riseup.net">olympiasds@riseup.net</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We're an anti-authoritarian, anti-capitalist, non-hierarchical, pro-queer, pro-feminist group dedicated to fighting all forms and systems of oppression, both locally and internationally, movin</p></teaser>
    <content><p>We&#039;re an anti-authoritarian, anti-capitalist, non-hierarchical, pro-queer, pro-feminist group dedicated to fighting all forms and systems of oppression, both locally and internationally, moving towards a free world based on joy and desire.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Students for Justice in Palestine</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/TESCSJP">https://www.facebook.com/TESCSJP</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tescsjp@gmail.com">tescsjp@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Evergreen Students for Justice in Palestine supports a just and fair resolution to the Israel/Palestine conflict.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Evergreen Students for Justice in Palestine supports a just and fair resolution to the Israel/Palestine conflict. SJP seeks to undermine the Israeli ethnic cleansing and occupation of Palestine through engagement in Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions movement and by organizing educational events and exhibits.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Students United for Reproductive Justice (SURJ)</title>
    <teaser><p>Students United for Reproductive Justice is a student run group that works to increase awareness, education, dialogue, and action around reproductive health, reproductive rights, and reproductive j</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Students United for Reproductive Justice is a student run group that works to increase awareness, education, dialogue, and action around reproductive health, reproductive rights, and reproductive justice. S.U.R.J. works to end reproductive oppression and stigma in the Evergreen and Olympia community by addressing the pro-choice movement as a matter of bodily autonomy, health, and socioeconomic paradigms.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Student Video Gamers Alliance (SVGA)</title>
    <teaser><p>The Student Video Gamer's Alliance exists to bring students together around gaming culture on campus and in the local community.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Student Video Gamer&#039;s Alliance exists to bring students together around gaming culture on campus and in the local community. By bringing students and other gamers into the same physical space we facilitate social engagement and encourage students to participate with campus activities who would not otherwise do so.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Bee Club</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/The-Evergreen-Bee-Club/302023706606459">https://www.facebook.com/pages/The-Evergreen-Bee-Club/302023706606459</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>To provide the Evergreen community with a space in which to study the practice of beekeeping, and access to information about the behavior and significance of bees and other local pollinators.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>To provide the Evergreen community with a space in which to study the practice of beekeeping, and access to information about the behavior and significance of bees and other local pollinators.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Campus Stewards</title>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Campus Stewards will strive to increase the beauty, productivity and sustainability of the campus and its students.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Campus Stewards will strive to increase the beauty, productivity and sustainability of the campus and its students. It is our goal to involve the student body in upkeeping its campus, leading projects that will enhance the sense of community and generate a feeling of accountability throughout.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Chamber Orchestra</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://facebook.com/evergreenchamberorchestra">http://facebook.com/evergreenchamberorchestra</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenchamberorchestra@live.com">evergreenchamberorchestra@live.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to provide Evergreen students with the opportunity to play their orchestral instruments in a relaxed and friendly atmosphere. We are also a performance group.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to provide Evergreen students with the opportunity to play their orchestral instruments in a relaxed and friendly atmosphere. We are also a performance group. We are dedicated to bringing a variety of orchestral music and the culture surrounding it the Evergreen students and our local communities.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Conservation Corps</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/tesc.tecc?_rdr=p">https://www.facebook.com/tesc.tecc?_rdr=p</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:buildatrail@gmail.com">buildatrail@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We intend to establish a student group with the mission of maintaining, preserving and protecting Evergreen's natural landscape.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>We intend to establish a student group with the mission of maintaining, preserving and protecting Evergreen&#039;s natural landscape. We will emphasize &quot;leave no trace&quot; practices, outdoor ethics and forest safety so those who join us play an active role in promoting environmental awareness and safety practices for the campus forest.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Fiber Arts</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/evergreenfiber.artsclub.9">https://www.facebook.com/evergreenfiber.artsclub.9</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenfiberarts@gmail.com">evergreenfiberarts@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Evergreen Fiber Arts Club provides a supportive community space for many to come as beginners to learn or as skilled individuals to improve their craft.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Evergreen Fiber Arts Club provides a supportive community space for many to come as beginners to learn or as skilled individuals to improve their craft. We seek to empower community members by teaching them practical skill in fiber work and assisting them in exploring the potential of this field of study as hobby, study, or profession. We do this through providing weekly gatherings, workshops, a library of resources and networking with the larger community as a sustainable and intentional manner.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Political Information Center</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/EPICEvergreenStateCollege">http://www.facebook.com/EPICEvergreenStateCollege</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:EPICevergreen@gmail.com">EPICevergreen@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>EPIC is an organization of people to the political left.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>EPIC is an organization of people to the political left. We seek to create a sustained community of educational, political and environmental concern: one bringing together progressives, radicals, activists, scholars, students, faculty, staff, and community groups. We maintain a vision of a democratic society, where at all levels the people have control of the decisions which affect them and the resources on which they are dependent. In short, we believe that the principle of democracy should be applied to all forms of social organization and relations. We seek a relevance necessary to effect change at the most basic levels of economic, political, and social organization. We feel the urgency to put forth a radical, democratic, program counterposed to authoritarian movements. Our goal is to bring about critical awareness of the issues which affect our lives. We want to demystify the reality we face in order to help ourselves and others understand and creatively deal with our everyday lives and our futures before us.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Queer Alliance (EQA)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Evergreen-Queer-Alliance/140201512710891">http://www.facebook.com/pages/Evergreen-Queer-Alliance/140201512710891</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:eqa@evergreen.edu">eqa@evergreen.edu</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The EQA hopes to create a safe space for members of the LGBTQ+ community at Evergreen. They also hope to create social change.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>The EQA hopes to create a safe space for members of the LGBTQ+ community at Evergreen. They also hope to create social change.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Shakespeare Society</title>
    <teaser><p>We are an intrepid group of theater enthusiasts striving to promote the wonderful work of the world&#039;s pre-eminent playwright.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>We are an intrepid group of theater enthusiasts striving to promote the wonderful work of the world&#039;s pre-eminent playwright.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Shellfish Club</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/shellfishclub">https://www.facebook.com/shellfishclub</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenshellfishclub@gmail.com">evergreenshellfishclub@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The mission of the Evergreen Shellfish Club is to provide a hands-on, educational experience through shellfish aquaculture and wild harvest; to develop and maintain a strong commitment to water qua</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of the Evergreen Shellfish Club is to provide a hands-on, educational experience through shellfish aquaculture and wild harvest; to develop and maintain a strong commitment to water quality and our access to healthy marine resources.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Hip Hop Congress</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/TheEvergreenStateCollegeHipHopCongress">https://www.facebook.com/TheEvergreenStateCollegeHipHopCongress</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:teschhc@gmail.com">teschhc@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Hip Hop Congress is dedicated to educating, empowering, and uniting individuals through Hip Hop.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Hip Hop Congress is dedicated to educating, empowering, and uniting individuals through Hip Hop. We preserve and evolve Hip Hop by inspiring social action and culture creativity within the community.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Student Media Project</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Evergreen-Student-Music-Project/216250611445">http://www.facebook.com/pages/Evergreen-Student-Music-Project/216250611445</a></li>
<li><a href="http://blogs.evergreen.edu/esmp">http://blogs.evergreen.edu/esmp</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="https://soundcloud.com/esmp-2015">https://soundcloud.com/esmp-2015</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:audiointern@gmail.com">audiointern@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Student Media Project has been a traditional at our college for over 30 years, although it used to be the "music" project.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Student Media Project has been a traditional at our college for over 30 years, although it used to be the &quot;music&quot; project. Students are encourages to submit a demo of an original musical composition to the ESMP group who then selects a number of tracks equal to the number of student enrolled in the Advanced Multi-track class, and those students then bring in their assigned artists to the audio studios on campus to re-record the composition. Those versions of the composition are ultimately compiled and made into an audio CD accompanied by a separate media drive that provides additional forms of student-derived media; animation, pictures, etc. The final works presented do not only showcase the creative efforts of Evergreen students but also the technological resources that our college has to offer. The ESMP is also important to the Advanced Multi-track class because their recordings will serve as their Week 10 projects for winter quarter, and the entire process will offer them invaluable real-life audio engineering experience. The ESMP group will hold weekly meetings &amp; perhaps host some fundraisers.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Animal Agriculture Collective</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Evergreen-Animal-Agriculture-Collective-126259020734124/">https://www.facebook.com/Evergreen-Animal-Agriculture-Collective-126259020734124...</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://essaapasturedlamb.wixsite.com/sheepclub">http://essaapasturedlamb.wixsite.com/sheepclub</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:essaapasturedlamb@gmail.com">essaapasturedlamb@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The mission of Evergreen Animal Agriculture Collective is to create and encourage opportunities for experimental and practical learning in animal agriculture to Evergreen students.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of Evergreen Animal Agriculture Collective is to create and encourage opportunities for experimental and practical learning in animal agriculture to Evergreen students.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM2 D3107</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays @ 1:30 - 2:30pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Thinkers Society</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/evergreenthinkers/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/evergreenthinkers/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Evergreen: Gee, Thinkers Society, what do you want to do this week? Thinkers Society: The same thing we do every week, Evergreen, try to take over the world!</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>Evergreen: Gee, Thinkers Society, what do you want to do this week? Thinkers Society: The same thing we do every week, Evergreen, try to take over the world!</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Vocal Ensemble </title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/EvergreenVocalEnsemble/?fref=ts">https://www.facebook.com/EvergreenVocalEnsemble/?fref=ts</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenvocalensemble@gmail.com">evergreenvocalensemble@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Evergreen Vocal Ensemble is an all inclusive company of singers on campus and in the community.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Evergreen Vocal Ensemble is an all inclusive company of singers on campus and in the community. As a group, regardless of singing level, we create and perform a repertoire of various genres of a capella music. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Yoga Service Collective</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Evergreen-Yoga-Service-Collective-450477078396431/">https://www.facebook.com/Evergreen-Yoga-Service-Collective-450477078396431/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenyogaservicecollective@gmail.com">evergreenyogaservicecollective@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Yoga Service Collective is a group dedicated to living Yoga as a path and a practice for holistic sustainability.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Yoga Service Collective is a group dedicated to living Yoga as a path and a practice for holistic sustainability. TEYSC provides a space for students to practice and learn about yoga service, sustainable action and whole health, applying learning through service, to others as well as to personal wellbeing. We hold weekly classes and meetings, as well as service projects, workshops and other events. Our projects and events are learning based, and centered around service, sustainability, yoga and health.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>For Racial Justice</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/ForRJ">https://www.facebook.com/ForRJ</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:forrj@riseup.net">forrj@riseup.net</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>For Racial Justice (ForRJ) is a group seeking to confront racism at the Evergreen State College, and our wider community.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>For Racial Justice (ForRJ) is a group seeking to confront racism at the Evergreen State College, and our wider community. We wish to assist other campus groups with anti-racist actions, host spaces to address racial privilege, and acknowledge intersecting forms of oppression. ForRJ also looks to celebrate the human diversity overshadowed by racial categories, including cultures and ancestries obscured under the notion of whiteness. Through creative expression and anti-racist education, we aspire to work toward collective liberation.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>FIST! (Feminist In Solidarity Together)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/fist.tesc?fref=ts">http://www.facebook.com/fist.tesc?fref=ts</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://fistatevergreen.tumblr.com/">http://fistatevergreen.tumblr.com/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:raiseyourfist@riseup.net">raiseyourfist@riseup.net</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>To provide a space for discussion and community around mtual aid, anti-oppression, with an emphasis on marginalized communities and voices.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>To provide a space for discussion and community around mtual aid, anti-oppression, with an emphasis on marginalized communities and voices.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Dance Co-op</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/TESCdancecoop">https://www.facebook.com/TESCdancecoop</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to hold space for embodiment and authentic expression through dance, music, and movement.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to hold space for embodiment and authentic expression through dance, music, and movement.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>COM  209</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays @ 6:00 - 9:00PM</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Gaming Guild</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreen.gaming.guild@gmail.com">evergreen.gaming.guild@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Gaming guild's mission is to provide a safe and fun environment for students and the community to get together, play games, and break the monotony of day-to-day.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Gaming guild&#039;s mission is to provide a safe and fun environment for students and the community to get together, play games, and break the monotony of day-to-day. Through the use of a variety of games, we can encourage the building of community and all-around fun for everyone.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>Student Activities CAB 313 - Big Wood Table</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Mondays 5pm-12am</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Generation Friends Comedy Arts Coalition</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=88426121533">http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=88426121533</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:generationfriends@gmail.com">generationfriends@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Generation Friends comedy arts coalition is Evergreen's student comedy troupe.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Generation Friends comedy arts coalition is Evergreen&#039;s student comedy troupe. Our goal is to create a community on campus of students engaged in sketch comedy, stand-up comedy, and improvisation. We strive to provide the evergreen community with various forms of entertainment while simultaneously creating a supportive environment for aspiring writers, actors, and directors. Our focus is not only to offer valuable training and experience to students interested in pursuing comedy as a career, but also to provide a creative outlet for any and all students who just want to make people laugh.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Mondays: COM 320 and COM 323 5:00 pm to 7:30 pm
Tuesdays: COM 308 5:00 pm to 7:00 pm
Fridays: COM 307 and 308  5:00 pm to 7:30 pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Geoduck Campus Games</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/117552941614418/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/117552941614418/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>We host the most unique and exciting theme and team-based games and related themed events for students to play on the Evergreen campus.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>We host the most unique and exciting theme and team-based games and related themed events for students to play on the Evergreen campus.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 Plaza</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Weekly meetings every other Friday starting October 7th from 5-8pm at the Big Wood Table in Student Activities.
                                            Humans Vs. Zombies - Saturdays 9 pm - midnight</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Geoduck Student Union</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://blogs.evergreen.edu/geoduckunion/">http://blogs.evergreen.edu/geoduckunion/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:GeoduckUnion@evergreen.edu">GeoduckUnion@evergreen.edu</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Geoduck Union is the official representation of the student body at The Evergreen State College.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Geoduck Union is the official representation of the student body at The Evergreen State College. The Union is committed to unifying students across all Evergreen campuses, serving their interests at the local, state, and national levels and empowering all students to participate in positive social and political chance while fostering a fair and diverse community. The Union works to improve student quality of life by advocating for students&#039; rights and needs, facilitating communication among students, and ensuring a fair balance of power among faculty, staff, administration and students.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>CAB 301</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays 1-3 pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories>Governance</categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Giant Robot Appreciation Society (GRAS)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://chibichibicon.net/">http://chibichibicon.net/</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/groups/EvergreenGRAS/">http://www.facebook.com/groups/EvergreenGRAS/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenchibicon@gmail.com">evergreenchibicon@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>To spread the love of anime to the community!!!</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>To spread the love of anime to the community!!!</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 D1107</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Mondays 3:30-5:30pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Graphic Novel Union</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/EvergreenComicsClub">http://www.facebook.com/EvergreenComicsClub</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreengnu@gmail.com">evergreengnu@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The GNU is an arts and media club focused on the creation and celebration of comics.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The GNU is an arts and media club focused on the creation and celebration of comics. Writers, illustrators, artists of all kinds, and comics enthusiasts can expect to collaborate on independent comics and discuss all forms of sequential art from around the world. The club offers reading materials and art supplies for its members, and produces at least one zine a year.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 C2107</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Mondays @ 3:30 - 5:30pm </meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>All God&#039;s People</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://allgodspeopletesc.org/">http://allgodspeopletesc.org/</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/164207203610023/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/164207203610023/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>All God's People is a multi-ethnic community on campus exploring spirituality by looking at the life of Jesus.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>All God&#039;s People is a multi-ethnic community on campus exploring spirituality by looking at the life of Jesus. We do this through weekly meetings together for discussion with activities to further process what we are discovering as well as small groups to promote growth and physical, spiritual, and social well being. We welcome people with any background or beliefs.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>CAB 301</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Tuesdays @ 5:30pm -8:30pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Greeners Association for Psychedelic Studies (GAPS)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/446213498758359/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/446213498758359/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:gapsatevergreen@gmail.com">gapsatevergreen@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Greeners Association for Psychedelic Studies (GAPS) is a group devoted to discussing the value of psychedelics for medical, therapeutic, spiritual, and scientific application.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Greeners Association for Psychedelic Studies (GAPS) is a group devoted to discussing the value of psychedelics for medical, therapeutic, spiritual, and scientific application. We are not here to encourage or discourage substance use but rather to allow the free flow of information. Our weekly meetings consist of presentations from members, documentaries, risk reduction information, and lively discussion. All are welcome to attend. We hope you will come explore with us.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>CAB 301</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Thursdays @ 4:00 - 5:00pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Hacker Club</title>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Hacker Club is a collection of individuals interested in learning, discussing, and implementing real-world applications of advanced technological subjects.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Hacker Club is a collection of individuals interested in learning, discussing, and implementing real-world applications of advanced technological subjects. We focus on topics chosen by the membership, and regularly host workshops for the group to share their skills with each other. Hacker Club is also home to the GNU-e-Ducks, Evergreen&#039;s competitive cyber-security team.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Abolish Cops and Prisons</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://acap.interference.cc/">http://acap.interference.cc/</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/Abolish-Cops-and-Prisons/425962244188693">https://www.facebook.com/pages/Abolish-Cops-and-Prisons/425962244188693</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:acap@lists.riseup.net">acap@lists.riseup.net</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We are a group of students at Evergreen seeking to undermine the prison and police system through prisoner solidarity and support by offering educational and media events, holding monthly prisoner </p></teaser>
    <content><p>We are a group of students at Evergreen seeking to undermine the prison and police system through prisoner solidarity and support by offering educational and media events, holding monthly prisoner writing days, and to organize campaigns against injustices related to police and prisons.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Hui o Pasifika</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/180604245700463/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/180604245700463/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:Huiopasifika@gmail.com">Huiopasifika@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Hui o Pasifika strives to celebrate and educate others about Pacific Islander culture and issues through food, art, workshops, and other events.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>Hui o Pasifika strives to celebrate and educate others about Pacific Islander culture and issues through food, art, workshops, and other events.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Bike Shop</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:theevergreenbikeshop@gmail.com">theevergreenbikeshop@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Bike Shop is a student-led, community-run, do-it-yourself bike shop that is open to the entire Olympia area.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Bike Shop is a student-led, community-run, do-it-yourself bike shop that is open to the entire Olympia area. Our goal is to provide various resources to the community in order to promote cycling as an active lifestyle as well as educate people regarding alternative transportation issues. The shop provides an alternative to the often prohibitive nature of bike repair and culture both in financial cost and accessibility. By maintaining a free learning environment where anyone, student or not, can develop skills of bike self-reliance, the shop encourages a developing ethic of environmental and social consciousness.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Black Student Union</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/67366822068/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/67366822068/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:escbsu@gmail.com">escbsu@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The purpose of the Black Student Union (BSU) is to provide unity amongst those who identify with Black Peoples, while engaging with the Evergreen community through cultural, educational, and entert</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The purpose of the Black Student Union (BSU) is to provide unity amongst those who identify with Black Peoples, while engaging with the Evergreen community through cultural, educational, and entertaining activities.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Body Love Burlesque</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:bodyloveburlesque@gmail.com">bodyloveburlesque@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Body Love Burlesque is an organization of students dedicated to spreading body acceptance of all shapes, sizes, colors, ages, and gender identities.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Body Love Burlesque is an organization of students dedicated to spreading body acceptance of all shapes, sizes, colors, ages, and gender identities. We will achieve this with skill building through crafts, costume and prop making, teamwork, fashion and performance. This group will be open to anyone interested in challenging societal norms and exploring their freedom of expression regardless of prior experience.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Campus Food Coalition</title>
    <teaser><p>The Campus Food Coalition provides a forum for the Evergreen community to address food stores on campus as a focal point for issues that impact folks regionally, nationally, and internationally.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Campus Food Coalition provides a forum for the Evergreen community to address food stores on campus as a focal point for issues that impact folks regionally, nationally, and internationally.  We promote community ethics and sustainability goals via our campus food system.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Capoeira Angola</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:capoeira.angola@evergreen.edu">capoeira.angola@evergreen.edu</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to provide the opportunity to study, practice, and experience Capoeria Angola to the Evergreen community.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to provide the opportunity to study, practice, and experience Capoeria Angola to the Evergreen community.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Chemistry and Other Sciences (ChAOS)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://facebook.com/groups/tescchaos">http://facebook.com/groups/tescchaos</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:chemclub@evergreen.edu">chemclub@evergreen.edu</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Chemistry and Other Sciences club's principle functions are a) to foster opportunities for students of science at The Evergreen State College to get involved in community and pro</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Chemistry and Other Sciences club&#039;s principle functions are a) to foster opportunities for students of science at The Evergreen State College to get involved in community and professional activities, b) to support and promote science education, especially as it relates to sustainable practices, both in the Evergreen and broader South Sound community. Finally, the club will play an important role in the social facet of the student body, engendering a sense of community among science students at Evergreen.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 D2107</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays @ 1:00pm - 2:00pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Chess Club</title>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Chess Club is devoted to creating a space that offers an opportunity to learn and play chess to participants of all skill levels.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Chess Club is devoted to creating a space that offers an opportunity to learn and play chess to participants of all skill levels. We will work towards introducing chess and popularizing the sport to all members of campus and the surrounding community.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Circus Resurgence</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/2318237909/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/2318237909/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Evergreen Circus Resurgence is an inclusive student group devoted to the practice of circus arts.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Evergreen Circus Resurgence is an inclusive student group devoted to the practice of circus arts. We are an open forum that welcomes people of all skill levels to play, practice, learn and teach at our weekly meetings. We provide the equipment, encouragement, and environment for everyone from seasoned professionals to absolute beginners to feel comfortable trying new tricks and honing their craft.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays &amp; Saturdays 5-8 pm in LIB 3000.</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Clean Energy Committee</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/committee/cleanenergy/home.htm">http://www.evergreen.edu/committee/cleanenergy/home.htm</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/tesccec">http://www.facebook.com/tesccec</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:cleanenergy@evergreen.edu">cleanenergy@evergreen.edu</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The mission of the Clean Energy Committee is to support the success of energy efficiency, renewable energy, and resource conservation at Evergreen.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of the Clean Energy Committee is to support the success of energy efficiency, renewable energy, and resource conservation at Evergreen. The Clean Energy Committee is a group of students collaborating with campus staff and faculty. It carries the responsibility of representing the student body while appropriating the Clean Energy Fund. This fund was established by the students of Evergreen State College to fuel the progress of renewable energy in the Northwest.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories>Governance</categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Coalition Against Sexual Violence (CASV)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/evergreencasv?fref=nf">https://www.facebook.com/evergreencasv?fref=nf</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tesccasv@gmail.com">tesccasv@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We strive to provide peer advocacy and resources for survivors of sexual assault,domestic violence, and emotional abuse at TESC.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>We strive to provide peer advocacy and resources for survivors of sexual assault,domestic violence, and emotional abuse at TESC. We will also train students every year about advocacy and provide workshops about sexual violence and domestic violence consent.  These resources are open to folks of all genders, orientations, and identities. We work to create a safer, educated campus community.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Common Bread</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/groups/10676204182/">http://www.facebook.com/groups/10676204182/</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://cbread.blogspot.com/">http://cbread.blogspot.com/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Common Bread is a culturally diverse student group on campus aiming to create a safe haven to honor the spiritual journey. We hope to create a contemplative still point in our ever turning world.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Common Bread is a culturally diverse student group on campus aiming to create a safe haven to honor the spiritual journey. We hope to create a contemplative still point in our ever turning world. We share food, wisdom, and experience through group discussions and creative explorations. Our biggest goal is to make sure every voice is heard, and every soul is nourished.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>Organic Farmhouse</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Thursdays 5 - 8:30pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Community Gardens</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/ecogardens">http://www.facebook.com/ecogardens</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://commiegardens.blogspot.com/">http://commiegardens.blogspot.com/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:TESCcommunitygardens@gmail.com">TESCcommunitygardens@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to maintain a shared space for the Evergreen and greater community to practice organic gardening.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to maintain a shared space for the Evergreen and greater community to practice organic gardening. The Evergreen Community Gardens will provide the tools and seeds for success, both literally and metaphorically. We organize workshops and work-parties emphasizing responsible, ecological gardening practices and the importance of local food systems. The Evergreen Community Gardens aims to form a strong and supportive community, and to instill the love of organic gardening in new gardeners which will hopefully last a lifetime.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Cooper Point Journal</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://www.cooperpointjournal.com">http://www.cooperpointjournal.com</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/evergreencpj">http://www.facebook.com/evergreencpj</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Cooper Point Journal organization members commit their efforts to two primary purposes: compiling submissions from students at large to create a newspaper that focuses on and reflects the student c</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Cooper Point Journal organization members commit their efforts to two primary purposes: compiling submissions from students at large to create a newspaper that focuses on and reflects the student citizens of The Evergreen State College and examines how matters, particularly within the college, affect and involve students. The newspaper - also named Cooper Point Journal - serves as a medium for informing and entertaining students and as a forum for the ideas and opinions of students and others.The learning laboratory aspect of the CPJ organization manifests itself by developing and maintaining effective and responsible managing of operations and finances of an endeavor (newspaper) organization, as well as dealing with such life challenges as organizing efforts to develop and maintain an inclusive organization, establishing a group culture of inclusive and responsible decision making, personal and collective accountability, leadership that focuses of fulfilling organization goals and objectives by fostering an environment of consensus and cooperation rather than focusing on the decision-making authority and responsibilities of leadership, confronting injustice and discrimination.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Creative Cures</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/groups/481761261946124/">http://www.facebook.com/groups/481761261946124/</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/creativecures">http://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/creativecures</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Creative Cures is a meeting of minds to discover and implement innovative approaches towards treating and curing diseases of both physiological and psychological origin that afflict the unfortunate</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Creative Cures is a meeting of minds to discover and implement innovative approaches towards treating and curing diseases of both physiological and psychological origin that afflict the unfortunate in our community and all over the globe.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen State Permaculture</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100002159888751">http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100002159888751</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:demetergarden@gmail.com">demetergarden@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Evergreen State Permaculture utilizes and stewards Demeter's Garden --a student-run permaculture demonstration site near The Organic Farm.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Evergreen State Permaculture utilizes and stewards Demeter&#039;s Garden --a student-run permaculture demonstration site near The Organic Farm. Aside from completing general maintenance in the garden, it is used to experiment with perennial polycultures and work towards implementing the master plan.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Electronic Music Collective</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://facebook.com/theemcevergreen">http://facebook.com/theemcevergreen</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:theevergreenemc@gmail.com">theevergreenemc@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Electronic Music Collective seeks to provide an atmosphere of revelry for electronic music to flourish. We wish to appreciate the history of electronic music’s origins, as well as its future.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Electronic Music Collective seeks to provide an atmosphere of revelry for electronic music to flourish. We wish to appreciate the history of electronic music’s origins, as well as its future. As a collective we will work on the production of events to spread awareness of this culture, and promote overall joy within the community. What’s your life’s soundtrack?</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Greener Engineering Cooperative</title>
    <teaser><p>The Greener Engineering Cooperative will collaborate on a variety of projects using the techniques of electrical, mechanical, software, and civil engineering.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>The Greener Engineering Cooperative will collaborate on a variety of projects using the techniques of electrical, mechanical, software, and civil engineering.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>MPA Student Union</title>
    <teaser><p>The MPA Student Union is the independent organization which functions to serve the academic, professional, and social will of the students in the MPA (general and tribal) cohorts at The Evergreen S</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The MPA Student Union is the independent organization which functions to serve the academic, professional, and social will of the students in the MPA (general and tribal) cohorts at The Evergreen State College.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Jewish Student Union</title>
    <teaser><p>To provide a religious &amp; cultural outlet for Jewish Students &amp; Allies.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>To provide a religious &amp; cultural outlet for Jewish Students &amp; Allies.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Musicologists</title>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Musicologists are a student group committed to the academic study of music and its cultural contexts.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Musicologists are a student group committed to the academic study of music and its cultural contexts. Through active participation in musical happenings, such as performances, workshops, and lectures on and off campus, members of the club will develop a rich understanding of the role of music in societies.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Clarity Dance Collective</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/711529352214278/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/711529352214278/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:claritydance@gmail.com">claritydance@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to provide an outlet for students to engage in choreographed dance pieces by offering them the opportunity to learn, facilitate, and perform works of art.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to provide an outlet for students to engage in choreographed dance pieces by offering them the opportunity to learn, facilitate, and perform works of art.  Clarity strives to honor a wide variety of styles and encourage each member to explore their creative potential in a fun and inclusive environment.  We welcome all skill levels and support our members as they pursue a passion for dancce.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>D20 - Tabletop Roleplaying Club</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/366736053490937/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/366736053490937/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>D20 is a student organization created to provide a place for students to gather with like-minded gamers and journey together through dungeons and worlds throughout the various platforms of tabletop</p></teaser>
    <content><p>D20 is a student organization created to provide a place for students to gather with like-minded gamers and journey together through dungeons and worlds throughout the various platforms of tabletop roleplay gaming.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Psychology Club</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/1475438066051010/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/1475438066051010/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to bring together people to discuss and share ideas and knowledge pertaining to the field of psychology. Our aim will be to explore the subject in an open and free environment.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to bring together people to discuss and share ideas and knowledge pertaining to the field of psychology. Our aim will be to explore the subject in an open and free environment. We hope to create a better understanding of psychology in a way that is beneficial to both club members and the community.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Greener 2 Greener</title>
    <teaser><p>Greener 2 Greener is an organization that serves to connect Evergreen students with the support they need to flourish in a collegiate environment in the form of peer counceling as well as social an</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Greener 2 Greener is an organization that serves to connect Evergreen students with the support they need to flourish in a collegiate environment in the form of peer counceling as well as social and activity networking.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>We Are Able</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://weareable.jcink.net/index.php">http://weareable.jcink.net/index.php</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tescable@gmail.com">tescable@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We stand together to create an environment where every individual is accepted, respected, and loved. C = Companionship A = Advocacy R = Recognition E = Education S = Solidarity</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>We stand together to create an environment where every individual is accepted, respected, and loved. C = Companionship A = Advocacy R = Recognition E = Education S = Solidarity</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Players&#039; Club </title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/nomulligans/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/nomulligans/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:ryanmwilson22@yahoo.com">ryanmwilson22@yahoo.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Players' Club exists to support the Magic: The Gathering club community.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Players' Club exists to support the Magic: The Gathering club community. Holding a consistent space for Magic: The Gathering players to meet and build skills from beginner level to competitive level. The club will host magic events and build a collection of cards to support the above. Overall we're here to have fun. Lunch time Magic happens on demand.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>Quiet Lounge 2nd floor CAB building</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Tuesdays and Thursdays, between 5:30 and 7:30</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Warriors</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenwarriors@yahoo.com">evergreenwarriors@yahoo.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Warriors spread positivity and inspiration throughout The Evergreen State College.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Warriors spread positivity and inspiration throughout The Evergreen State College. Hand-in-hand, we will work together to make Evergreen a comfortable, positive place for students today, tomorrow, and for as long as we exist.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Black Cottonwood Collective</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/EPICEvergreenStateCollege/">https://www.facebook.com/EPICEvergreenStateCollege/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:theblackcottonwoodcollective@riseup.net">theblackcottonwoodcollective@riseup.net</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Black Cottonwood Collective is an anti-authoritarian student group which seeks to equip Evergreen students with radical resources, skills and analysis. </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>The Black Cottonwood Collective is an anti-authoritarian student group which seeks to equip Evergreen students with radical resources, skills and analysis. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>3D Alternative Recycled Materials (3D ARM)</title>
    <teaser><p>The mission of 3D ARM is to explore the interdisciplinary opportunities and applications of 3D printing.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of 3D ARM is to explore the interdisciplinary opportunities and applications of 3D printing. We will make accessible the physical and educational components of a 3D printing experience. We will explore and create alternative printer filaments and recycle used filament for future use. We will promote and offer the resource of 3D printers to all Evergreen students and programs regardless of 3D printing experience.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>DIY Audio Circuits</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:diyaudiocircuitz@gmail.com">diyaudiocircuitz@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>DIY Audio Circuits Club is a student group created with the intention of bringing people together who are interested in learning about building and understanding circuitry that can be used for audi</p></teaser>
    <content><p>DIY Audio Circuits Club is a student group created with the intention of bringing people together who are interested in learning about building and understanding circuitry that can be used for audio purposes. Our meetings will be a place where people from all backgrounds of experience can come to learn from each other and participate in lectures and workshops. We will learn about electrical components, circuits, how to use tools for building and testing electronics, and build projects together. We value spreading the knowledge of building circuitry because it is a valuable skill to have.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Vagina Monologues</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:TESCVAGMONS2015@gmail.com">TESCVAGMONS2015@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Vagina Monologues is a catalyst that promotes creative events to increase awareness, raise money, and revitalize the spirit of existing anti-violence organizations.The Vagina Monologues, suppor</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Vagina Monologues is a catalyst that promotes creative events to increase awareness, raise money, and revitalize the spirit of existing anti-violence organizations.The Vagina Monologues, supported by the organization V-day, generates broader attention for the fight to stop violence against women and girls.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Free Nestora</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://www.freenestora.org">http://www.freenestora.org</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="https://es-es.facebook.com/LibertadParaNestoraFreedomforNestora">https://es-es.facebook.com/LibertadParaNestoraFreedomforNestora</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:freenestora.olympia@gmail.com">freenestora.olympia@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Nestora Salgado is an indigenous leader, US citizen, and political prisoner in Mexico. She was arrested for her leading role in a community self-defense network.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Nestora Salgado is an indigenous leader, US citizen, and political prisoner in Mexico. She was arrested for her leading role in a community self-defense network. The Free Nestora committee seeks her release through deploying a multiplicity of tactics: solidarity demonstrations, material support, symbolic actions, and engaging legislators.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Food Not Bombs!</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://foodnotbombs.net/washington.html">http://foodnotbombs.net/washington.html</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:olyfoodnotbombs@gmail.com">olyfoodnotbombs@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Food Not Bombs club is an independent student group that supports Food Not Bombs in Olympia. We meet to discuss policies that affect giving people food.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Food Not Bombs club is an independent student group that supports Food Not Bombs in Olympia. We meet to discuss policies that affect giving people food. Food Not Bombs volunteers meet at Media Island, 816 Adams St, Olympia, WA 98501, on Saturdays at 2:30pm to make food and serve at the Olympia Timberland Library at 4:30pm.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Pagans</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/evergreenstatepagans?fref=ts">https://www.facebook.com/evergreenstatepagans?fref=ts</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:embrown1995@gmail.com">embrown1995@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We are a safe space for pagan Evergreen students and alumni. We help connect members to the local pagan community and provide support.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>We are a safe space for pagan Evergreen students and alumni. We help connect members to the local pagan community and provide support. We also provide educational workshops for those interested in psychic training and/or meditations.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 D2107</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Fridays @ 3pm - 4pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Rock and Gem Club</title>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Rock and Gem Club looks at the world from the viewpoint of rocks. We are about revealing the underground world of natural treasure that also tell geological stories.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Rock and Gem Club looks at the world from the viewpoint of rocks. We are about revealing the underground world of natural treasure that also tell geological stories. We can then hilight these treasures in our lapidary studio by grinding, cutting and polishing our rocks. It will also be a place to make jewelry. By joining the Rock and Gem Club, you will learn about our surrounding areas geologically and go on adventure Rock hunts! A group that is sure to enhance everyone's knowledge and deepen our appreciation of Earth! ((Not to be taken for Granite ;) ))</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Mental Health Collective</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:TescMHC@gmail.com">TescMHC@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>With emotional well being and mental health in mind, Mental Health Collective aims at providing a safe space for everyone.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>With emotional well being and mental health in mind, Mental Health Collective aims at providing a safe space for everyone. We work to provide access to resources and community support for people struggling with or affected by mental illness. We work to address the mental health needs of the Evergreen community. All struggles welcome.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Trail Blazers</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:stijac20@evergreen.edu">stijac20@evergreen.edu</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The trailblazers mission is to build, maintain, and provide safe passage for all students, and residents of Thurston County through the Evergreen woods.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The trailblazers mission is to build, maintain, and provide safe passage for all students, and residents of Thurston County through the Evergreen woods. Students and citizens should be able to safely enjoy the forest while having a minimal impact on the environment around them.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen A Cappella</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:acapellaevergreen@gmail.com">acapellaevergreen@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The mission of the Evergreen A Cappella group is to create excellent music while having fun and learning in the process.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of the Evergreen A Cappella group is to create excellent music while having fun and learning in the process.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Masters of Environmental Studies Association</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:MESstudentAssociation@gmail.com">MESstudentAssociation@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Masters of Environmental Studies Association (MESA) is committed to supporting MES students in their professional development.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Masters of Environmental Studies Association (MESA) is committed to supporting MES students in their professional development. We also organize the annual Rachel Carson Forum, which provides a public space to raise important environmental concerns within our community. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Mycophiles</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenmycophiles@gmail.com">evergreenmycophiles@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Mycophiles' mission is to broaden the understanding and love for the world of fungi, to inspire amateur mycologists and carry out projects in the fields of cultivation, remediation, a</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Mycophiles' mission is to broaden the understanding and love for the world of fungi, to inspire amateur mycologists and carry out projects in the fields of cultivation, remediation, and waste stream utilization. As foragers they promote responsible harvesting techniques and work to cultivate a deeper connection to our natural systems. They are open to collaborations with the larger community in order to create an interconnected body of knowledge that mimics the mycelial mats that they love so.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Why Am I?</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:troybacon48@gmail.com">troybacon48@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>'Why am I?' is a student group where students will share knowledge of astrology and human design, so Evergreen students can gain a greater understanding of their innate personality, as well as othe</p></teaser>
    <content><p>'Why am I?' is a student group where students will share knowledge of astrology and human design, so Evergreen students can gain a greater understanding of their innate personality, as well as others' personalities, to promote tolerance and acceptance. Students work to realize and cultivate their unique talents and purpose in their life and the world.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>SOS Brigade</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tescsosbrigade@gmail.com">tescsosbrigade@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The sole goal of the SOS Brigade is to make the world a more interesting place.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The sole goal of the SOS Brigade is to make the world a more interesting place. We will accomplish this three ways: by hosting meetings in a comfortable and structure environment, investigating bizarre phenomena and releasing a newsletter of findings, and participating in events to foster cooperation between already established SOS brigades as well as promote the creation of new brigades.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Russian Club</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/RussianClubatTESC?fref=ts">https://www.facebook.com/RussianClubatTESC?fref=ts</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="http://collabtest.evergreen.edu/cms/%40TESCRussianClub">http://collabtest.evergreen.edu/cms/%40TESCRussianClub</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:russianatevergreen@gmail.com">russianatevergreen@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Through Russian Club, we plan to promote education and understanding of Russian language, life, culture, history, and customs within The Evergreen State College and the broader community.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Through Russian Club, we plan to promote education and understanding of Russian language, life, culture, history, and customs within The Evergreen State College and the broader community. We will carry out this goal by planning events that connect our community to Russian culture, such as bake sales featuring authentic Russian recipes, events corresponding to russian holidays and significant events, as well as attending local celebrations and events pertaining to Russian culture.  </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 A2107</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Tuesdays 4-6 pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Animal Liberation Collective</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/EvergreenAnimalLiberationCollective?fref=ts">https://www.facebook.com/EvergreenAnimalLiberationCollective?fref=ts</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:animalliberationcollective@outlook.com">animalliberationcollective@outlook.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We are dedicated to the abolition of animal exploitation and seek to educate the public through outreach, advocacy, and demonstration.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>We are dedicated to the abolition of animal exploitation and seek to educate the public through outreach, advocacy, and demonstration.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Perennial Players Theatre Troupe</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://facebook.com/perennialplayers">http://facebook.com/perennialplayers</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:perennialplayers@gmail.com">perennialplayers@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Perennial Players is first and foremost, art with a meaning. Our goal is to create art through theatre that impacts the people who see the shows in one way or another.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Perennial Players is first and foremost, art with a meaning. Our goal is to create art through theatre that impacts the people who see the shows in one way or another. We have a focus on social justice shows, both straight plays and musicals. "Love the art in yourself, not yourself in the art."</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Students for Sensible Drug Policy</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://ssdp.org">http://ssdp.org</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/TESCSSDP">https://www.facebook.com/TESCSSDP</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:ssdptesc@gmail.com">ssdptesc@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Students for Sensible Drug Policy (SSDP) is an international grassroots organization founded in 1998.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Students for Sensible Drug Policy (SSDP) is an international grassroots organization founded in 1998. Comprised of students dedicated to ending the "war on drugs," SSDP neither condones or condemns drug use. The Evergreen chapter will host conversations about the realities of the "drug war" through regular meetings and events, promic youth civic engagement as a critical tool in reforming drug policy, connect with other groups addressing the collateral effects of US drug policy (EGYHOP, ACAB,etc.) and develop leaders who advocate for policy changes based on justice, liberty, compassion, and reason. With the support of SSDP's global networks, the Evergreen chapter will seek to implement sensible drug policy in a local, state, and national level, with a vision of fostering a healthier, safer, and freer global community. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Students for Sustainable Urban Design</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/GreenerUrbanDesign/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/GreenerUrbanDesign/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:greenerurbandesign@gmail.com">greenerurbandesign@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>SSUD consists of students who share a mutual interest in stainability and the places we live.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>SSUD consists of students who share a mutual interest in stainability and the places we live. From urban parks and maintaining wildlife and community gardens, to how humans function and how techonology and social ideas/policies can make cities and community thrive. We enjoy sharing articles, opportunities, and events we find, and discussing and designing projects for on campus. We also do activities such as group trips, bringing in speakers, watching films and TED talks, playing fun board games, (like catan) and more. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Students for Climate Action</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://jobscleanenergywa.com">http://jobscleanenergywa.com</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen affiliate of the Alliance for Jobs and Clean Energy; connecting students with opportunities for political action and grassroots activism against climate change. The Alliance for Jobs </p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen affiliate of the Alliance for Jobs and Clean Energy; connecting students with opportunities for political action and grassroots activism against climate change. The Alliance for Jobs and Clean Energy is Washington State's coalition of community organizations, business, labor, and environmental groups dedicated to reducing global warming pollution, creating family-wage jobs, and securing a better future for our families.We are boldly pursuing efforts to hold polluters accountable--accounting for the price of carbon pollution to reflect its true costs, and reinvesting in our Washington economy and communities. We are launching a Washington-based approach as part of a broader West Coast partnership that recognizes our critical role in addressing not just the local and regional impacts, but the global importance of curbing carbon pollution. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Embodied Arts Tribe (EAT)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://www.facebook.com/groups/embodiedartstribe">http://www.facebook.com/groups/embodiedartstribe</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>The Embodied Arts Tribe (EAT) is dedicated to cultivating a space for Evergreen students and community to learn, explore, and enjoy somatic movement, butoh dance and and movement meditation practic</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Embodied Arts Tribe (EAT) is dedicated to cultivating a space for Evergreen students and community to learn, explore, and enjoy somatic movement, butoh dance and and movement meditation practices. Our classes and workshops offer a unique opportunity to explore, awaken, and become empowered within our body-mind, through meditative exercises that open the doors to deeper levels of expression, embodiment, and self-discovery. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 A3107</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Saturdays 9:30am-3:30pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Phrontisterion</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/1651801958423227/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/1651801958423227/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tescphrontisterion@gmail.com">tescphrontisterion@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>To foster a community of classical studies at TESC, to improve and inspire mehods of classical teaching, and to create a solid foundation for future students interested in the classics to come, are</p></teaser>
    <content><p>To foster a community of classical studies at TESC, to improve and inspire mehods of classical teaching, and to create a solid foundation for future students interested in the classics to come, are all the main foci of the Phrontisterion.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Music Circle</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/EvergreenMusicCircle/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/EvergreenMusicCircle/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>A Music Circle is a kind of gathering often seen at folk festivals and sci-fi conventions where musicians sit in a circle and take turns playing songs, jamming, reading poetry, or whatever else unt</p></teaser>
    <content><p>A Music Circle is a kind of gathering often seen at folk festivals and sci-fi conventions where musicians sit in a circle and take turns playing songs, jamming, reading poetry, or whatever else until such time as everyone is too tired to continue. We do that. At Evergreen. Thus, the Evergreen Music Circle. Come Play!</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Hemp Club</title>
    <teaser><p>The purpose of The Hemp Club is to get the Evergreen State College on the Department of Agricultural Pilot program to do research into the industrail hemp industry for the state of Washington.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The purpose of The Hemp Club is to get the Evergreen State College on the Department of Agricultural Pilot program to do research into the industrail hemp industry for the state of Washington. We will build an outline based on the Federal and State guidelines. Students will work in the different areas of research and will present it  to the state legislature when they reconvene in January. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Open Source Technology Club</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:EvergreenOSTC@gmail.com">EvergreenOSTC@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Making an all inclusive environment which empowers individuals to utilize and produce open source designs in a collaborative society</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>Making an all inclusive environment which empowers individuals to utilize and produce open source designs in a collaborative society</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>The Evergreen Go Club</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreengoclub@gmail.com">evergreengoclub@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>To spread the art, philosophy, and culture of  the ancient game of go by playing the game and sharing in a lush culture over 2,500 years old.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>To spread the art, philosophy, and culture of  the ancient game of go by playing the game and sharing in a lush culture over 2,500 years old. We will look at art, anime, and film while we practice the aesthetics and etiquette that make go so popular around the world. We wish to create a comfortable space for players of all skills (including those just starting out). Go is especially welcoming, with a built in system to create even matches between players of different skill levels. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Master in Teaching Student Association</title>
    <teaser><p>The mission of the Master in Teaching Student Association is to enhance teacher preparation at the Evergreen State College by providing extracurricular services to future educators that support the</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of the Master in Teaching Student Association is to enhance teacher preparation at the Evergreen State College by providing extracurricular services to future educators that support them in their pre-professional development. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Student Media Project</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://blogs.evergreen.edu/esmp">http://blogs.evergreen.edu/esmp</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Student Media Project is a 36-year-old running tradition of music composed, performed, recorded, and produced by Evergreen students in collaboration with Student Activities, Electroni</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Student Media Project is a 36-year-old running tradition of music composed, performed, recorded, and produced by Evergreen students in collaboration with Student Activities, Electronic media, and the Advanced Multi-Track Composition program. This project aims to promote creativity by giving students an outlet for their art, both visual and musical. Our group consists mostly of audio recording students from the Advanced Audio Recording program, Intro to Audio Recording class and the Electronic Media Interns. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Web Team Testing Club</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:nelsone@evergreen.edu">nelsone@evergreen.edu</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We try out things in Drupal to see if Student Groups are being created or updated properly. It's lots of fun and you should join.</p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>We try out things in Drupal to see if Student Groups are being created or updated properly. It's lots of fun and you should join.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Broad Arts Club</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Broad-Arts-180971868904843/">https://www.facebook.com/Broad-Arts-180971868904843/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:broadartsofficial@gmail.com">broadartsofficial@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The goal of Broad Arts Club is to be a unique and diverse art club, unlike any art club the world has ever seen. A place where experimentation and creation meet.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The goal of Broad Arts Club is to be a unique and diverse art club, unlike any art club the world has ever seen. A place where experimentation and creation meet. We will explore a multitude of medias, materials, and more. Arts include, but are not limited to; casting, costume-fabrication, movie-making, make-up, music, etc. Fun at every meeting!</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Astronomical Society</title>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Astronomical Society is a student run group with the goal of bringing the cosmos closer to home.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Astronomical Society is a student run group with the goal of bringing the cosmos closer to home. We want to understand the tools and methods used to observe our galaxy and beyond. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 C2109</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Mondays 3-4pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Makeup Collab</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:theevergreenmakeupcollab@gmail.com">theevergreenmakeupcollab@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Makeup Collab is here to provide expert help with makeup for all people. We encourage people of any skill to come and join us in learning.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Makeup Collab is here to provide expert help with makeup for all people. We encourage people of any skill to come and join us in learning. We will be exploring many different kinds of make up: stage, runway, period, photography, special effects, bridal, and beauty. You will get a chance to practice on yourself and others in an open and accepting community of people who have a love of makeup. We will also be learning more about skin care, makeup products, ingrediants, and some history of makeup. Another aspect we hope to talk and enlighten others about is makeup associated with gender/gender roles and how that binary is being challenged. With that said, we will welcome all people with any level of experience with open arems into the beauty community of Evergreen. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Go Club</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/evergreengoclub/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/evergreengoclub/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreengoclub@gmail.com">evergreengoclub@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Go Club aims to spread the art, philosophy, and culture of the ancient game of go by plaing the game and sharing in a lush culture over 2,500 years old.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Go Club aims to spread the art, philosophy, and culture of the ancient game of go by plaing the game and sharing in a lush culture over 2,500 years old. We will look at art, anime, and film while we practice the aesthetics and etiquette that make go so popular around the world. We wish to create a comfortable space for players of all skill levels including those just starting out. Go is especially welcoming with a built-in system to create even matches between players of different skill levels. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>ASL Club</title>
    <teaser><p>The ASL Club's mission is to educate and create a Deaf-inclusive space on campus and in the olympia community. </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>The ASL Club's mission is to educate and create a Deaf-inclusive space on campus and in the olympia community. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen-Olympia Community Drumline</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://Facebook.com/olympiadrumline">http://Facebook.com/olympiadrumline</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>We are an Evergreen-Olympia community drumline illuminating social justices and progressive change through artistic activism and community organizations. </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>We are an Evergreen-Olympia community drumline illuminating social justices and progressive change through artistic activism and community organizations. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>El Club de Español</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenspanishclub@gmail.com">evergreenspanishclub@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The purpose of el Club de Español is to provide educational opportunities outside of the classroom for those interested in Spanish language and culture.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The purpose of el Club de Español is to provide educational opportunities outside of the classroom for those interested in Spanish language and culture. This club also provides the opportunity to meet with other Evergreen students &amp; faculty interested in speaking Spanish</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Greeners for Bernie</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/1051630044881935/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/1051630044881935/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:Greeners4Sanders@gmail.com">Greeners4Sanders@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Greeners for Bernie is here to get Bernie Sanders elected as president by phone banking, rallies, and other election events.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Greeners for Bernie is here to get Bernie Sanders elected as president by phone banking, rallies, and other election events.  We are also here to support progressive fights in Washington and the U.S.A.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 E2105</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Tuesdays 4:15-5:15pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Archery Club</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/617203888328764/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/617203888328764/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenarchery13@gmail.com">evergreenarchery13@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Archery Club offers a safe place where students who want to practice and partake in archery can do so on campus.  We provide all equipment that is necessary and can provide tips and s</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Archery Club offers a safe place where students who want to practice and partake in archery can do so on campus.  We provide all equipment that is necessary and can provide tips and some instruction for individuals who are interested in the sport.  We use both recurve and compound bows for our sessions.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Collaboration Nation</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:CNartistcollective@gmail.com">CNartistcollective@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>A friendly environment for any type of artist to collaborate with one another and create projects. As well as to prepare them for success as a working artist in today's society. </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>A friendly environment for any type of artist to collaborate with one another and create projects. As well as to prepare them for success as a working artist in today's society. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 E3105</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Thursdays @ 5:00-7:00pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Gateways Student Alliance</title>
    <teaser><p>The mission of the Student Group portion of the Gateways for Incarcerated Youth Program is to facilitate the work of TESC scholars and Gateways participants for cultivating the needs of prospective</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of the Student Group portion of the Gateways for Incarcerated Youth Program is to facilitate the work of TESC scholars and Gateways participants for cultivating the needs of prospective students transitioning from incarceration. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Queer Underground: Evergreen&#039;s Experimental Nightshow (QUEENs)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/thequeerunderground/">https://www.instagram.com/thequeerunderground/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tescqueerunderground@gmail.com">tescqueerunderground@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to create a safe and exciting atmosphere for queer and trans students to learn and execute different aspects of queer performance.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to create a safe and exciting atmosphere for queer and trans students to learn and execute different aspects of queer performance. We provide workshops and performance opportunities to boost our members' confidence and skills in experimental performance arts that include but are not limited to: burlesque, drag, and group acts. We strive to cultivate a community creation of uncensored expression of self.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Unconditional Pawsitivity</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/UnconditionalPawsitivity/timeline">https://www.facebook.com/UnconditionalPawsitivity/timeline</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:unconditional.pawsitivity@gmail.com">unconditional.pawsitivity@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The purpose of our organization is to provide Evergreen students, faculty, and staff and the local community instant stress relief through animal assisted therapy.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The purpose of our organization is to provide Evergreen students, faculty, and staff and the local community instant stress relief through animal assisted therapy.  Handlers along with their animals will be involved in various activities around campus and the community in an effort to give those who need a reason to smile, a reason to do so!</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Society of Women Engineers</title>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to stimulate women to achieve full potential in careers as engineers and leaders, expand the image of the engineering profession as a positive force in improving the quality of life,</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to stimulate women to achieve full potential in careers as engineers and leaders, expand the image of the engineering profession as a positive force in improving the quality of life, and demonstrate the value of diversity.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Mental Health Alliance</title>
    <teaser><p>Evergreen Mental Health Alliance aims to provide peer support and resources for students struggling with their mental welfare and others who wish to learn more, as well as raise awareness and desti</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Evergreen Mental Health Alliance aims to provide peer support and resources for students struggling with their mental welfare and others who wish to learn more, as well as raise awareness and destigmative mental illness. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Black Focus</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/832347860243320/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/832347860243320/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:blackfocus@gmail.com">blackfocus@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>To create and foster a safe space for Black-identifying students at The Evergreen State College - with recognition and space made for LGBTQIA and disabled folks.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>To create and foster a safe space for Black-identifying students at The Evergreen State College - with recognition and space made for LGBTQIA and disabled folks. We will hold sacred the spectrum of Blackness in its many forms, recognizing that Blackness is not a monolith.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Student Veterans Organization</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:TESCVETS@gmail.com">TESCVETS@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Evergreen Student Veterans Organization's mission is to create a safe space for Veterans and thier families, and we will provide resources and connections for student Veterans.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>The Evergreen Student Veterans Organization's mission is to create a safe space for Veterans and thier families, and we will provide resources and connections for student Veterans. The Evergreen Student Veterans Organization will advocate for student Veterans' rights. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>Veterans Resource Center (LIB 1002)</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays 3:30 pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Philosopher&#039;s Union</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:PhilosophersUnionEvergreen@gmail.com">PhilosophersUnionEvergreen@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Welcome to the Philosopher's Union; we are a student group aiming to create an open forum for the philosophical discourse.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Welcome to the Philosopher's Union; we are a student group aiming to create an open forum for the philosophical discourse. Students are welcome to participate in discussions, regardless of education or skill level - all are welcome! Students who join the Philosopher's Union can expect regular discussions, readings, analytical games, open panel discussions, and guest speakers. We are non-partisan organization of civil discourse through clarity and illumination. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 D3105</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Mondays 3-5pm | Fridays 2-4pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Amnesty International</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:TESCAmnesty@gmail.com">TESCAmnesty@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Creating "a world in which every person - regardless of race, religion, ethnicity, sexual orientation or gender identity - enjoy all of the human rights enshrined in the Universal Declaration of Hu</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Creating "a world in which every person - regardless of race, religion, ethnicity, sexual orientation or gender identity - enjoy all of the human rights enshrined in the Universal Declaration of Human Rights." We hope to build on this mission by educating the Evergreen community and empowering them to take action against human rights abuses. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>Sem 2 D2107</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays 5-6pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen International Community</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/evergreenintcom/?fref=ts">https://www.facebook.com/evergreenintcom/?fref=ts</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenintcom@gmail.com">evergreenintcom@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>To provide resources and connections for international, immigrant, first-generation, and multicultural students. To contribute and connect with the Evergreen community across cultural divides. </p></teaser>
    <content><p>To provide resources and connections for international, immigrant, first-generation, and multicultural students. To contribute and connect with the Evergreen community across cultural divides. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>Big Wood Table in CAB 313</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Mondays @ 5:00 - 6:00PM</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Philosophers Union</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:skoaid26@evergreen.edu">skoaid26@evergreen.edu</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser></teaser>
    <content></content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 D2105</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates><div class="date-repeat-rule">Repeats every week every Friday 6 times. </div><span class="date-display-single" property="dc:date" datatype="xsd:dateTime" content="2016-04-22T14:00:00-07:00">Friday, April 22, 2016 - 2:00pm</span>, <span class="date-display-single" property="dc:date" datatype="xsd:dateTime" content="2016-04-29T14:00:00-07:00">Friday, April 29, 2016 - 2:00pm</span>, <span class="date-display-single" property="dc:date" datatype="xsd:dateTime" content="2016-05-06T14:00:00-07:00">Friday, May 6, 2016 - 2:00pm</span>, <span class="date-display-single" property="dc:date" datatype="xsd:dateTime" content="2016-05-13T14:00:00-07:00">Friday, May 13, 2016 - 2:00pm</span>, <span class="date-display-single" property="dc:date" datatype="xsd:dateTime" content="2016-05-20T14:00:00-07:00">Friday, May 20, 2016 - 2:00pm</span>, <span class="date-display-single" property="dc:date" datatype="xsd:dateTime" content="2016-05-27T14:00:00-07:00">Friday, May 27, 2016 - 2:00pm</span></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Friday Weekly Meetings 2-4pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Literary Society</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:EvergreenLiterarySociety@gmail.com">EvergreenLiterarySociety@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We as a literary society intend to cultivate a space wherein artistically inclined people can come together and hone thier work.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>We as a literary society intend to cultivate a space wherein artistically inclined people can come together and hone thier work. Within our group, we will enable members to share, create, and perform. We as writers, intend to foster productivity through routine sessions - having noted that we often fall into the trap of creative stanation. Our goal is to meet and empower each other to move past our creative blocks.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>COM 320</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Tuesdays 6-8pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Young Democrats</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/825464367598842/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/825464367598842/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>To promote progressive policies and leaders, and to civically engage our campus through a variety of activities.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>To promote progressive policies and leaders, and to civically engage our campus through a variety of activities. We wish to incite discussion and dialogue about social justice, economic, and polotical conditions that perpetuate and legitimize current power structures. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Zine Club</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:2ndBestZineCollective@gmail.com">2ndBestZineCollective@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>The Zine Club will create a safe place for Queer, LGBTQ, female and POC students. Additionally, the Zine Club will build a community through art, outreach, and archive. </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>The Zine Club will create a safe place for Queer, LGBTQ, female and POC students. Additionally, the Zine Club will build a community through art, outreach, and archive. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Write/Hear</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:writehearevergreen@gmail.com">writehearevergreen@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Write/Hear is an on campus writing support group (separate from the Writing Center) where members meet weekly in a non-academic setting to share, work, create and collaborate in a low-stress settin</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Write/Hear is an on campus writing support group (separate from the Writing Center) where members meet weekly in a non-academic setting to share, work, create and collaborate in a low-stress setting. Our goal is to foster creativity through routine sessions and new prompts. We hope to help empower each other's authorship through active practice and oral presentation. Members participate in weekly meetings, provide a strong foundation of support, and find methods of overcoming artistic stagnation, or "writer's block." </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>SEM 2 D3109</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesday @ 1:30pm</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen RPG Guild</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://facebook.com/groups/568152276707399">http://facebook.com/groups/568152276707399</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenrpgguild@gmail.com">evergreenrpgguild@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>United by our love of role playing games, The Evergreen RPG Guild is dedicated to creating a safe space where Evergreen students can discuss, organize, and play tabletop RPG's together.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>United by our love of role playing games, The Evergreen RPG Guild is dedicated to creating a safe space where Evergreen students can discuss, organize, and play tabletop RPG's together. We're always welcoming new players so come and join us!</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>Quiet Lounge - CAB 201</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Wednesdays @ 5:30 - 8:30PM </meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Greener P.A.W.S. (Predator and Wildlife Support)</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="http://facebook.com/evergreenpaws">http://facebook.com/evergreenpaws</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenpaws@gmail.com">evergreenpaws@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>As citizens who recognize the vital role that predators such as wolves, bears, big cats, and coyotes play in maintaining a healthy ecosystem, we will advocate for their protection. </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>As citizens who recognize the vital role that predators such as wolves, bears, big cats, and coyotes play in maintaining a healthy ecosystem, we will advocate for their protection. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Mini Generals</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:ryanmwilson22@gmail.com">ryanmwilson22@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We build, paint, and then battle minitures in a clan style. We welcome all to come join and play for a clan or solo.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>We build, paint, and then battle minitures in a clan style. We welcome all to come join and play for a clan or solo. Among the Generals we need builders, painters, and people who just want to hang out.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Community Gardens</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Evergreen-Community-Garden-326188574155690/">https://www.facebook.com/Evergreen-Community-Garden-326188574155690/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tesccommunitygardens@gmail.com">tesccommunitygardens@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to maintain a shared space for the Evergreen and greater community to practice organic gardening.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to maintain a shared space for the Evergreen and greater community to practice organic gardening. The Evergreen Community Gardens will provide the tools and seeds for success, both literally and metaphorically. We organize workshops and work-parties emphasizing responsible, ecological gardening practices and the importance of local food systems. The Evergreen Community Gardens aims to form a strong and supportive community of gardeners that will all learn, teach and grow together. The group also strives to strengthen the bonds between Evergreen, Evergreen alumni, and the surrounding community, and to instill the love of organic gardening in new gardeners which will hopefully last a lifetime. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Clay Club </title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/TheEvergreenStateCollegePotteryClub/">https://www.facebook.com/TheEvergreenStateCollegePotteryClub/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to provide a safe space for beginner and intermiedate clay artists alike to share a community space that provides learning opportunities, i.e.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to provide a safe space for beginner and intermiedate clay artists alike to share a community space that provides learning opportunities, i.e. workshops, guest artist lectures, and special firing events. We hope to provide opportunities to the community to grow in their skills and find a new passion. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Ladies in Tech </title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/evergreenladiesintech/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/evergreenladiesintech/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Ladies in Tech (LiT) is committed to creating a welcoming and safe community for those who feel under represented in the technology industry and for those who are committed to diversifying the fiel</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Ladies in Tech (LiT) is committed to creating a welcoming and safe community for those who feel under represented in the technology industry and for those who are committed to diversifying the field by providing learning and career resources and workshops to help it's members succeed in school, gain experience and find employment after college. In addition, LiT has a dedicated resource, the GNU-E-Ducks, for those who are particularly interested in learning about cyber security. Facebook: Evergreen Ladies in Tech (Lit)</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Dance Co-op</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/search/1421501624750318/local_search?surface=tyah">https://www.facebook.com/search/1421501624750318/local_search?surface=tyah</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to hold space for embodiment and authentic expression through dance, music, and movement. </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to hold space for embodiment and authentic expression through dance, music, and movement. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>COM 209</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Contact Improv &amp; Consent meetings: Tuesdays:  Nov. 15, Nov. 29, Dec. 6 @ 4:30 - 6:30PM</meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Film Club</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/1833236190246582/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/1833236190246582/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:audr.romp@gmail.com">audr.romp@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Film Club is here to appreciate the power and beauty of movies. There are many different approaches to presenting visual image.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Film Club is here to appreciate the power and beauty of movies. There are many different approaches to presenting visual image. Film combines self expression, technology and imagination to move viewers emotionally, and film club wants to acknowledge that. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Musicians Guild</title>
    <teaser><p>Our mission is to foster the all-ages DIY music scene for students living on campus by providing a safe space where creative expression is encouraged. </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>Our mission is to foster the all-ages DIY music scene for students living on campus by providing a safe space where creative expression is encouraged. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates><span class="date-display-single" property="dc:date" datatype="xsd:dateTime" content="2016-10-11T17:00:00-07:00">Tuesday, October 11, 2016 - 5:00pm</span></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Chinese Culture Club</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:evergreenchinesecultureclub@gmail.com">evergreenchinesecultureclub@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>We are passionate about facilitating a student group that will allow Evergreen students and community members to experience, share and learn about Chinese culture.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>We are passionate about facilitating a student group that will allow Evergreen students and community members to experience, share and learn about Chinese culture. In this group we will explore subjects such as Tai Chi and Qi Gong, tea culture, Chinese arts, cuisines and Daoism and other philosophies.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation>Longhouse 1002</meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong>Tuesdays @ 3:00 - 6:00PM </meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Young Americans For Liberty</title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://www.yaliberty.org/chapters/the-evergreen-state-college">http://www.yaliberty.org/chapters/the-evergreen-state-college</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/yalevergreen/">https://www.facebook.com/yalevergreen/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <teaser><p>The mission of Young Americans for Liberty is to identify, educate, train, and mobilize youth activists committed to "winning on principle." Our goal is to cast the leaders of tomorrow and reclaim </p></teaser>
    <content><p>The mission of Young Americans for Liberty is to identify, educate, train, and mobilize youth activists committed to "winning on principle." Our goal is to cast the leaders of tomorrow and reclaim the policies, candidates, and direction of our government. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Student-Workers Organizing Committee (S-WOC)</title>
    <teaser><p>S-WOC's mission is to create a space that builds solidarity among student workers and the greater Evergreen community.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>S-WOC's mission is to create a space that builds solidarity among student workers and the greater Evergreen community.  Through organizing and providing resources to guarantee basic rights of workers, students, and community members, we hope to foster solidarity and empower voices to be heard.</p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Active</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Vanishing Point Lit &amp; Art Magazine </title>
    <websites><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first"><a href="http://vanishingpointlitmag.wordpress.com">http://vanishingpointlitmag.wordpress.com</a></li>
<li class="last"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/vanishingpointmagazine/">https://www.facebook.com/vanishingpointmagazine/</a></li>
</ul></div></websites>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:tesc.vanishingpoint@gmail.com">tesc.vanishingpoint@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Vanishing Point is a literary magazine for the students and faculty of The Evergreen State College that showcases works of poetry, fiction, non-fiction, photography, art, and music.</p></teaser>
    <content><p>Vanishing Point is a literary magazine for the students and faculty of The Evergreen State College that showcases works of poetry, fiction, non-fiction, photography, art, and music. We aim to accurately represent the range of talent and artistic styles while creating an atmosphere of openess and accessibility to both our readership and the artists who submit their work. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Glassblowing Club</title>
    <email><div class="item-list"><ul><li class="first last"><a href="mailto:griffin.musser@gmail.com">griffin.musser@gmail.com</a></li>
</ul></div></email>
    <teaser><p>Glassblowing Club will exist to give participants access to the tools necessary to experiment with borosilicate or simply expose them to the medium of glassblowing.   </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>Glassblowing Club will exist to give participants access to the tools necessary to experiment with borosilicate or simply expose them to the medium of glassblowing.   </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates><span class="date-display-single" property="dc:date" datatype="xsd:dateTime" content="2016-11-04T11:15:00-07:00">Friday, November 4, 2016 - 11:15am</span></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
  <group>
    <title>Evergreen Musician&#039;s Guild</title>
    <teaser><p>To foster the all-ages DIY music scene for student living on campus by providing a safe space where creative expression is encouraged. </p>
</teaser>
    <content><p>To foster the all-ages DIY music scene for student living on campus by providing a safe space where creative expression is encouraged. </p>
</content>
    <meetinglocation></meetinglocation>
    <meetingdates></meetingdates>
    <meetingtimelong></meetingtimelong>
    <featured>Not featured</featured>
    <categories></categories>
    <active>Inactive</active>
  </group>
</groups>
