<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<pages>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/biology</url>
  <title>Biology and Life Sciences</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:06</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T10:10:18</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode>Biological Sciences</directorycode>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Examine life at the cellular level. Find new ways to cure disease. Survey marine
    organisms in their Puget Sound and Pacific Ocean habitats. Delve into the complex relationship
    between mathematical models and experimental results. Share your passion for science.&#160;</p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Vertebrate Evolution" class="image-full" src="images/biology/vertebrate-evolution.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Jordan Falloon (left) and Phoenix Green (middle) study an assortment of
     animal bones with help from faculty Heather Heying in the program Vertebrate Evolution.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Whether you want to study biology to prepare for a career in medicine or the health
    professions, for a teaching career in secondary schools, as part of your liberal arts education,
    or as a prerequisite for graduate study in science, Evergreen&#8217;s mixture of
    interdisciplinary study and hands-on lab and field research will teach you how to apply
    scientific principles to solving real-world problems.</p>
   <p>Studying science at Evergreen is a different experience than what science majors get at most
    universities. Here biology, chemistry, physics, and other disciplines are woven together,
    providing a unique interdisciplinary education. From high-tech labs to field studies,
    you&#8217;ll develop an appreciation of the levels of organization of life, their diversity, and
    how physical, chemical, and geological processes have shaped life on earth.</p>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">Numerous research students present their work at scientific meetings and
     have been authors on technical papers.</p>
   </div>
   <p>At Evergreen, you&#8217;ll immediately begin learning to use sophisticated scientific
    equipment to answer complex biological questions. Many year-long science programs begin with
    foundational work and quickly transition to student research projects so that all students gain
    scientific skills. You&#8217;ll also have opportunities to do scientific research as part of
    faculty research programs. Numerous students present their work at scientific meetings and have
    been authors on technical papers.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world.</strong></p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Students use a microscope" class="image-full"
     src="images/biology/scanning-electron-microscope.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">David Ginocchio studies cross-sections of cottonwood leaves in the Scanning
     Electron Microscope. Ginocchio is working with Clarissa Dirks on Identification of a Novel
     Virus in Populus Freemontii.</p>
   </div>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <div class="box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <div class="media media-alt">
     <div class="media-img">
      <a href="../about/alumni/sarahiggins.htm">
       <img alt="Sara Higgins" src="images/profile-sara.jpg"/>
      </a>
     </div>
     <div class="media-body">
      <p><a href="../about/alumni/sarahiggins.htm"><strong>Sara Higgins &#8217;08</strong></a>
       pursued her dream to become a doctor.</p>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <p>Evergreen biology graduates have an excellent record of success in graduate and professional
    schools, as well as working in a variety of scientific and technical fields. An Evergreen
    biology degree prepares you for jobs in laboratories, universities, or industry, and is
    excellent preparation for earning a graduate degree. It can be your springboard into
    professional school, where you&#8217;ll train to become a physician, dentist, veterinarian, or
    attorney. Or you can earn a teaching certificate so you can teach in high-demand science in K-12
    schools. You&#8217;ll also be well prepared for a career in sales and marketing in
    science-related industries. The possibilities are limited only by your energy and ambition.</p>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <h3>Science Laboratories</h3>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">The phage lab has been a center for undergraduate research at Evergreen
     since 1972, where involved students analyze these natural disease-fighting bacteriophages.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Students of all levels have access to science labs with a full range of equipment and
    high-tech tools. Our students have unique opportunities to conduct scientific research using
    high-quality instruments, such as a scanning electron microscope and a nuclear magnetic
    resonance spectrometer. In addition, they use some of the best modern software available.</p>
   <h3>Computer Applications Lab (CAL)</h3>
   <p>The CAL supports the campus community with computing technologies for scientific inquiry.</p>
   <h3>Phage Biology Lab</h3>
   <p>The phage lab has been a center for undergraduate research at Evergreen since 1972. Today,
    there are generally 10 to 15 students involved in work in the lab, analyzing these natural
    disease-fighting bacteriophages. Students have presented at various recent regional, national,
    and international meetings, including the biennial Evergreen International Phage Biology
    meetings.</p>
   <p>Students enrolled in Introduction to Natural Sciences will isolate, characterize, and annotate
    mycobacteriophage genomes, name them, and send the isolates to collections housed at the Howard
    Hughes Medical Institute and the University of Pittsburgh. This innovative year-long lab series
    will engage students in true scientific discovery and give them the opportunity to contribute to
    ongoing research of the Science Education Alliance&#8217;s Phage Hunters Advancing Genomics and
    Evolutionary Science Project.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <a class="lazy-load" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ck57nqYFMYQ">
     <img alt="Video: Molecule to Organism in the Field" src="images/biology/video-thumbnail.jpg"/>
    </a>
    <p class="caption">Students in the Evergreen upper division science program Molecule to Organism
     undertook a study of the snails in Washington State. The work gave students with interests in
     molecular biology, plant biology, and ecology an opportunity to apply their interests in a team
     study. In this One Minute Evergreen, faculty Clarissa Dirks describes the project and its
     importance.</p>
   </div>
   <h3>Lab Stores</h3>
   <p>Goggles, lab coats, and a whole lot more, including teaching technicians who will help you
    determine what you need for your experiments.</p>
   <h3>Evergreen Ecological Observation Network (EEON)</h3>
   <p>EEON is a long-term research effort involving students and faculty conducting research in
    Evergreen&#8217;s 1,000-acre Puget Sound lowland second-growth rainforest. Their work is
    centered on 44 intensively studied long-term monitoring plots where they&#8217;re measuring
    biological diversity, development, carbon dynamics, and other characteristics.</p>
   <h3>Science Carnival and Research Exposition</h3>
   <p>The largest event of its kind in Washington, the Science Carnival offers hundreds of
    presentations from Evergreen science students with an emphasis on demonstration, hands-on
    participation and fun, plus a volcano! More than 1,000 elementary, high school and college
    students and community members crowd Red Square and the science labs to learn and get excited
    about science. Topics include chemistry, computer science, biology, food science, health,
    physics, optics, geology, marine science, and a wide range of other disciplines.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <img alt="Students study in the lab" class="illus-full" src="images/molecule-to-organism-12.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Students in the Molecule to Organism program complete their weekly laboratory
     work in organic chemistry and biology.</p>
   </div>
   <h3>Integrated Natural Science</h3>
   <p>
    <em>
     <small>Offered Fall 2017&#8211;Spring 2018</small>
    </em>
   </p>
   <p>We expect students to end the program with a working knowledge of scientific, mathematical,
    and computational concepts, ability to reason critically and to solve problems, and with
    hands-on experience in natural science. Students will also gain a strong appreciation of the
    interconnectedness of biological and physical systems, and an ability to apply this knowledge to
    complex problems.</p>
   <p>
    <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/integratednaturalscience-16304">View
     this program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Students in Marine Biology" class="image-full" src="images/biology/marine-biology.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Students in the summer Marine Biology program go sailing aboard the Resolute
     in Budd Inlet. Faculy Gerardo Chin-Leo had the students take plankton samples and salinity
     readings in the estuary. Students then drew illustrations of their findings.</p>
   </div>
   <img alt="Drawing the findings" class="image" src="images/biology/drawing.jpg"/>
  </sample>
  <projects>
   <ul class="text-list">
    <li>Isolation of bacteriophages for use as a biocontrol agent of <em>Yersinia ruckeri</em>, the
     salmonid pathogen</li>
    <li>Insights into HIV: Innate immunity of lemuriformes</li>
    <li>Illuminating oxygen deprivation in heart attacks: A novel method based on phosphorescence
     quenching</li>
    <li>Monitoring effects of atrazine and d<span class="looong-word"
      >ichlorodiphenyltrichloroethane</span> on the proliferation of MCF-7 cells <em>in
     vitro</em></li>
    <li>Optimization of a bacterially-mediated gene-based vaccine delivery system</li>
    <li>Semisynthesis of berberine derivative and its anti-cancer effects</li>
   </ul>
  </projects>
  <facultybios><p><strong>Andrew D. Brabban</strong> teaches molecular biology and biochemistry,
    focusing particularly on developing biotechnologies for agriculture, industry, and health care
    that improve the efficiency of a modern process or improve quality of life. His research
    includes the study of bacteriophages as model organisms in molecular genetics, as major players
    in microbial ecology, and as therapeutically important antimicrobials. He holds a Ph.D. in
    genetics and microbiology from the University of Liverpool, where he also earned a B.S. in
    microbial biotechnology.</p><strong>Clarissa Dirks</strong> aims to better understand the
   evolutionary principles that underlie the emergence, spread, and containment of infectious
   disease by studying the coevolution of retroviruses and their primate hosts. Her teaching and
   research interests include biology, microbiology, virology, and the integration of art and
   science. She also works with colleagues around the nation to examine and improve methods for
   teaching science, and received a major National Science Foundation grant to develop a science
   process and reasoning skills test. She earned her Ph.D. in molecular and cellular biology from
   the University of Washington, and holds a B.S. in microbiology from Arizona State
     University.<p><strong>Heather Heying</strong> focuses her teaching on evolutionary biology,
    zoology, animal behavior, and the philosophy of science. She has received grants to study
    speciation on islands, and her research has focused on the evolution of social behavior,
    particularly in tropical ecosystems. In the tropics she has worked primarily with amphibians and
    reptiles, including conducting one of the first long-term field studies in Madagascar. She
    earned her Ph.D. in biology at the University of Michigan, and her B.A. in anthropology from the
    University of California, Santa Cruz.</p></facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/business</url>
  <title>Business, Management, and Entrepreneurship</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:06</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T12:10:24</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode>Business and Economics</directorycode>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Learn how to create and manage innovative enterprises that bring about social
    change. Develop leadership skills. Start your own business. Gain a practical foundation in
    accounting, finance, marketing, and the other disciplines needed to operate in business and the
    larger world.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="The Organic Farm Stand" class="image-full" src="images/business/farm-stand.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">The Organic Farm sits at an interdisciplinary nexus of science, nature, and
     business.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Studying business at Evergreen gives you the tools to understand the relationship between
    business and society. Our programs cultivate a holistic understanding of the business world,
    taking into account social and environmental performance&#8212;along with financial
    returns&#8212;to measure the full impact.</p>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">You will develop the skills that characterize the far-thinking and
     effective organizational leader and manager.</p>
   </div>
   <p>In addition to learning the fundamentals of accounting, finance, marketing, economics, and
    statistics, students acquire the ability to read, comprehend, and interpret the internal and
    external flow of events impacting an organization. You will develop your skills in critical
    reasoning, communication, research, and strategic planning&#8212;skills that characterize the
    far-thinking and effective organizational leader and manager. A key focus here is on developing
    people skills and responsiveness to an organization&#8217;s stakeholders. Our courses in
    business and entrepreneurship are offered as full-time programs during the day and part-time
    programs during evenings and weekends.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world</strong>.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Chris Baggott" class="illus-full" src="images/business/chris-baggott.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Greener Chris Baggott was the co-founder of ExactTarget and recently launched
     his latest venture Compendium Software that focuses on organizational blogging and search
     engine optimization.</p>
   </div>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Olympia Coffee Roasting" class="image-full"
     src="images/business/olympia-coffee-roasting.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Greener Sam Schroeder&#8217;s co-owned business, the Olympia Coffee Roasting
     Company, was named Micro Roaster of the Year by Roast Magazine.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Evergreen Business graduates are prepared to do business. They create their own enterprises
    and work with or consult with others in founding or growing organizations. Our programs provide
    a solid foundation for graduate studies in business administration, public administration, and
    law. Our graduates are leaders in the private sector, government, and nonprofit
    organizations.</p>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">Evergreen Business graduates create their own enterprises and work with or
     consult with others in founding or growing organizations.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Evergreen offers students plenty of opportunities to gain practical, hands-on experience in
    business.</p>
   <p>Students run several enterprises on campus, including the <a
     href="http://blogs.evergreen.edu/theflamingeggplant/">Flaming Eggplant caf&#233;</a> and a farm
    stand that sells produce from the college&#8217;s <a
     href="http://www.evergreen.edu/organicfarm/home.htm">Organic Farm</a>.</p>
   <p>The <a href="http://www.greenerstore.org/">Greener Bookstore</a> provides student employment
    and career training. <a href="http://kaosradio.org/">KAOS</a>, Evergreen&#8217;s licensed radio
    station, depends on volunteers to operate, and the college&#8217;s newspaper, the <a
     href="http://www.cooperpointjournal.com/"><em>Cooper Point Journal</em></a> is staffed entirely
    by students (on both the editorial and business sides).</p>
   <p>Student Activities gives students the awesome ability to start their own clubs. In the past,
    students have established business-oriented clubs such as the Center for Sustainable
    Entrepreneurship, which <span>helped students learn about pursuing business careers.</span></p>
   <p>
    <span>Students can also find and connect with Greeners in many areas of business, both locally
     and around the world, through the online <a
      href="../alumni/_old-alumni/entrepreneurs/directory/index.htm">Alumni Entrepreneurs
      Directory</a>.</span>
   </p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>The Funding of Higher Education: Debt, the Great Divide!</h3>
   <p>
    <em>
     <small>Offered Fall 2017&#8211;Winter 2018<br/>
     </small>
    </em>
   </p>
   <p>How is college funded, and on whose dime? How much should a state or nation pay for the
    education of its citizens beyond secondary school, and to what extent should the expense of
    higher education fall upon individuals and their families?</p>
   <p>In this program, students will explore the financing of higher education as a case study
    through which they look at larger economic and social issues&#8212;and around which they build
    applicable skills in finance, economics, business, writing, communication, and research. What is
    the history of funding for higher education? How do various economic, social, and cultural
    models impact funding and society? What is the role of economics and finance? What about
    fundraising, grants, and scholarships? What are the related issues of social justice, equity,
    access, and political advocacy?</p>
   <p>The program will include lectures, seminars, workshops, films, and guest speakers. Students
    will participate in collaborative projects and research, and learn from a variety of community
    leaders.</p>
   <p>
    <a
     href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/thefundingofhighereducationdebtthegreatdivide-16307"
     >View this program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Business and management" class="image-full"
     src="images/business/business-and-mgmt.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Lecture and discussion in the program Business and Management Strategies for
     the Private and Public Sectors with Lee Lyttle and Theresa Aragon.</p>
   </div>
  </sample>
  <projects/>
  <facultybios>
   <p><strong>Glenn Landram</strong> focuses on finance, economics, and management science&#8212;the
    optimization side of business. Current research interests center around how to incorporate
    quantitative methods into business-related programs with variable student experience in
    mathematics. He earned his Ph.D. in management science from the University of Washington School
    of Business, M.S. in statistics from Oregon State University, and B.S. in mathematics from the
    University of Puget Sound.</p>
   <p><strong>Jon Baumunk</strong> has taught accounting and other business courses at San Diego
    State University, an online university, and several community colleges in San Diego. Previously,
    he taught and was a member of the senior staff at several law schools in Southern California.
    Before entering academia, Jon practiced law in Las Vegas and was an investment analyst and
    portfolio manager at a state pension fund, a mutual fund, a bank, and the world&#8217;s largest
    sovereign wealth fund.</p>
   <p><strong>Zo&#235; Van Schyndel</strong> is a Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA) who focuses on
    business, entrepreneurship, and sustainable investments at Evergreen. She was the practice
    leader of a green employee benefits consulting firm and has written about ethics, green tech,
    and socially responsible investing. A former regional manager at the Securities and Exchange
    Commission, she was instrumental in initiating one of the first socially responsible
    exchange-traded funds and led the development of the KLD/Russell Mellon family of socially
    responsible indexes. She earned her M.B.A. from Northeastern University.</p>
  </facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/chemistry</url>
  <title>Chemistry</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:06</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T10:39:05</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode>Chemistry</directorycode>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Discover the world around you at the atomic scale. Unravel the structure of
    organic compounds. Analyze trace metals in terrestrial and coastal ecosystems. Explore how you
    can contribute to the field of nanotechnology.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Waynant lecture" class="image-full" src="images/chemistry/waynant-lecture.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p class="caption">Students learn how different gases react upon being excited at the start of
      lecture for Introduction to Natural Science.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">Science at Evergreen weaves together disciplines and offers hands-on
     experience.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Chemistry is fundamental to understanding the world. Everything is made of chemicals, so
    chemistry touches almost every aspect of our existence. Chemical technologies provide solutions
    to problems in health care, materials, and energy generation and usage.<br/>
    <br/> Chemistry is often referred to as the central science because it unites physics and
    mathematics, biology and medicine, and the earth and environmental sciences.<br/>
    <br/> At Evergreen you can prepare for a career in science, medicine, or education through the
    study of chemistry. Discover this branch of science using quantitative methods and analytical
    tools. You'll study the relationship between molecular structure and function. You'll receive
    hands-on experience with modern lab techniques and research instrumentation.<br/>
    <br/> Evergreen students take part in a wide variety of activities: analyzing trace metals in
    soils, using spectroscopy to determine the structure of alkaloids, studying&#160;<span>chemical
     reactions critical to living systems</span>, and more. They can also attend professional
    scientific conferences such as annual meetings of the American Chemical Society, which has
    recognized the Evergreen Chemistry Club with several awards over the years.<br/>
    <br/> Our science faculty have expertise in a broad range of specialty areas. Our programs
    connect concepts in experimental chemistry to disciplines like biology, geology, and physics.
    Here, students engage in work that links theory to practice.<br/>
    <br/> By studying chemistry at Evergreen, you can develop the experience and skills that are
    essential for solving real world problems.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world.</strong></p>
   <figure class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Environmental analysis chem lab" class="image-full"
     src="images/chemistry/environmental-analysis-chem-lab.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p class="caption">Environmental Analysis students in a titrations lab.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <p>Evergreen chemistry graduates have an excellent record of success in graduate and professional
    schools, as well as working in a variety of scientific and technical fields. An Evergreen
    chemistry degree prepares you for careers in labs, universities, or industry and is excellent
    preparation for earning a graduate degree. It can be your springboard into professional school
    for training to become a physician, dentist, veterinarian, or attorney. Or you can earn a
    teaching certificate to teach high-demand science in K-12 schools. The possibilities are limited
    only by your energy and ambition.</p>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Environmental Analysis out in the field" class="image-full"
     src="images/chemistry/environmental-analysis.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Students in Environmental Analysis complete phase two of a research study of
     the chemical balance in river water with and without decaying salmon and leaf debris.</p>
   </div>
   <h3>Instrumentation</h3>
   <p>Students of all levels have access to modern chemical research instrumentation, including a
    400 MHz FT-NMR spectrometer with multinuclear capability, multiple FT-IR spectrometers, two
    GC-Mass spectrometers, an ICP-Mass spectrometer, an atomic absorption spectrometer, a CHN
    analyzer, a UV/Vis-Discrete autoanalyzer, a mercury analyzer and three ion chromatographs.</p>
   <h3>Laboratory Space</h3>
   <p>Evergreen has several dedicated laboratories designed specifically for instruction and
    research in chemistry including a state-of-the-art organic chemistry lab, a high-tech water
    quality analysis lab, an environmental analysis lab, two modern biochemistry and molecular
    biology labs, and general chemistry labs.</p>
   <h3>Computer Application Laboratory (CAL)</h3>
   <p>The CAL supports the campus community with computing technologies for scientific inquiry.</p>
   <h3>Science Support Center (SSC)</h3>
   <p>Goggles, lab coats, and a whole lot more, including teaching technicians who will help you
    determine what you need for your experiments.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement">
    <iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315"
     src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Uenir5wuxeQ" width="560"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>750 school kids + college level science experiments + cool fireworks and explosions = 2 days
      of learning and fun on Evergreen&#8217;s Olympia campus!</p>
     <p>Shot and edited by Annie Ferguson '15.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <h3>Science Carnival and Research Exposition</h3>
   <p>The largest event of its kind in Washington, the Science Carnival offers hundreds of
    presentations from Evergreen science students with an emphasis on demonstration, hands-on
    participation and fun. More than a thousand elementary, high-school and college students and
    community members crowd Red Square and the science labs to learn and get excited about science.
    Topics covered include chemistry, computer science, biology, food science, health, physics,
    optics, geology, marine science and a wide range of other disciplines.</p>
   <h3>The Evergreen Chemistry Club</h3>
   <p>A g<span>reat place for students interested in chemistry&#8212;and other scientific
     fields&#8212;to work together to promote science, learn more about careers, develop
     connections, and participate in interesting community and professional activities, including
     attending meetings of the American Chemistry Society (ACS). The club has won numerous national
     awards, including recognition in 2014 from the ACS as a Green Chemistry Student Chapter and an
     Honorable Mention Chapter.</span></p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>Scientific Explorations in Chemistry and Archaeology</h3>
   <p>
    <em>
     <small><em><small>Offered</small></em>&#160;Fall 2017&#8211;Spring 2018<br/>
     </small>
    </em>
   </p>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <img alt="Molecule to Organism" class="image-full" src="images/chemistry/m2o-chem-lab.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p class="caption">Students in the program Molecule to Organism spend Friday morning in organic
      chemistry lab.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>Though mass media portrays archaeologists as poison-arrow-ducking, Nazi-foiling adventurers,
    the truth is that archaeologists are scientists&#8212;and they often spend more time in the lab
    than finding the Ark of the Covenant. This program trains students to be such scientists.
    Incorporating archaeology, chemistry, math, research, and project presentation (written, oral,
    and visual), we seek to teach students all stages of the scientific method, from gathering data
    to presenting original research at conferences.</p>
   <p>The study will benefit students who are looking for general chemistry credits and who have an
    interest in archaeology. No previous experience in chemistry or archaeology is required, but
    students should be able to use a scientific calculator and have completed high school algebra.
    High school precalculus is strongly recommended.</p>
   <a
    href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/scientificexplorationsinchemistryandarchaeology-16159"
    >View this program in the catalog.</a>
   <br/>
   <figure class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Staged murder scene" class="image-full"
     src="images/chemistry/applied-bio-and-chem.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p class="caption">Students study for Applied Biology and Chemistry in Lab I.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <img alt="Staged murder scene" class="image-full" src="images/chemistry/crime-scene.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p class="caption">Students in the Forensics and Criminal Behavior program investigate staged
      murder scenes as part of a quarter-long investigation project.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
  </sample>
  <projects>
   <ul class="text-list">
    <li>Synthesis of bis-diphenylphosphinometallocene ligands for nickel catalyzed cross-coupling
     reactions</li>
    <li>Using <sup>1</sup>H-NMR spectroscopy to understand the effects of photosensitizers during
     photo-oxidation of lipids</li>
    <li>Synthesis of chitosan graft copolymers for biomedical applications</li>
    <li>Spatial correlation between arsenic and mercury contamination, mining, and microbes in
     southeastern Peru</li>
    <li>Synthesis and exploration of ferrofluids</li>
   </ul>
  </projects>
  <facultybios><strong>Dharshi Bopegedera</strong>&#8217;s teaching interests include general
   chemistry, applications of chemistry for non-science students, thermodynamics, quantum chemistry,
   instrumentation methods, and inorganic chemistry. Her scholarly work includes gas phase
   spectroscopy and developing novel experiments for the general chemistry and physical chemistry
   laboratories. She earned her Ph.D. in physical chemistry at the University of Arizona, her B.S.
   in chemistry with a mathematics minor from the University of Peradeniya in Sri-Lanka, and
   conducted post-doctoral research work in using spectroscopy to study kinetics of gas phase
   reactions at the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) in Boulder,
     Colorado.<p><strong>Lydia McKinstry</strong> focuses her teaching and research on organic
    chemistry, chemical synthesis, and NMR spectroscopy. Her interests include asymmetric synthesis
    methodology, chemical reaction dynamics, transition metal catalysis, and small molecule
    synthesis. One ongoing undergraduate research project involves the synthesis of a novel
    dipeptide analog molecule to be used in the development of specific protease enzyme inhibitors.
    Lydia earned a Ph.D. in organic chemistry at Montana State University, a B.S. in molecular cell
    biology with a minor in chemistry at Fort Lewis College, and conducted postdoctoral research in
    asymmetric synthesis methodology at the California Institute of Technology.</p><p><strong>Paula
     Schofield</strong> teaches polymer and industrial chemistry, organic chemistry, and
    biochemistry. She uses applied laboratory techniques and chemical instrumentation, along with
    collaborative problem solving to promote critical thinking skills. Her research involves
    undergraduates to synthesize biodegradable plastics and biomedical polymers with new and
    commercially applicable properties. She received two major NSF grants and is the director of
    Evergreen&#8217;s NSF S-STEM Scholarship program. She earned a Ph.D. in polymer chemistry from
    the University of Liverpool, a B.S. in chemistry and materials science from Manchester
    Metropolitan University, and did postdoctoral research in chemical engineering and materials
    science at Cornell University.</p></facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/computer-science</url>
  <title>Computer Science</title>
  <created>2013-12-09T16:20:06</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T10:29:51</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode/>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Code a compiler or simple operating system. Compete in national cybersecurity
    competitions. Create your own computer games. Build autonomous robots to navigate mazes.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Numbers: Creative Coding program" class="image-full"
     src="images/computer-science/creative-coding.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Students program circuit boards to play light patterns in LEDs.</p>
   </div>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">Apply your skills to practical problems using knowledge from other
     fields.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Studying computer science at Evergreen will give you the knowledge and tools to design, build,
    and understand complex computer systems. You&#8217;ll get to apply your skills to practical
    problems using knowledge from other fields, such as music, art, linguistics, physics,
    statistics, and ecology. Computer science is a dynamic and interdisciplinary field of study and
    Evergreen provides you with the opportunity to work on projects that apply theory to real
    problems and to participate in exciting challenges. For example, the program Computing Practice
    and Theory has combined the analysis of forest ecology data from the Pacific Northwest with
    machine learning. Computer science students at Evergreen have also participated in cybersecurity
    competitions, placing second in the Pacific Rim Collegiate Cyber Defense Competition.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Hao Nguyn, international student" class="image-full"
     src="images/computer-science/individual-study.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">International student Hao Nguyen works with a small group of fellow computer
     science students and faculty member Richard Weiss as part of his independent learning
     contract.</p>
   </div>
   <p>At Evergreen, you can explore computer science at a range of levels&#8212;whether you want to
    gain a basic understanding of how computers work or you plan to become a computer science
    researcher or professional.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world</strong>.</p>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <div class="box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <div class="media media-alt">
     <div class="media-img">
      <img alt="Sonia Scaer" src="images/computer-science/profiles-scaer.jpg"/>
     </div>
     <div class="media-body">
      <p>Sonia Scaer &#8217;96 is a software process delivery leader, technical project lead, and
       risk management engineering lead at GE Healthcare, Global Asset Management.</p>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <p>Our graduates have gone on to a range of professions, including working for Canonical (the
    developer of the Linux Ubuntu operating system), a medical software startup, and as developers
    for F5 Networks (which makes network routers and firewalls), IT specialists for Twitter, and
    software engineers for Washington state.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Interactive Sound and Video" class="image-full"
     src="images/computer-science/interactive-sound-and-video.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Ben Kamen introduces audio programming with the program Max on the first day
     of Interactive Sound and Video.</p>
   </div>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement">
    <p class="pull-quote">You&#8217;ll work on projects that apply theory to real problems and
     participate in exciting challenges.</p>
   </div>
   <h3>Academic Computing Center</h3>
   <p>As Evergreen&#8217;s computing hub, the center has four computing classrooms and offers
    printers, scanners, and a commons area that boasts more than 50 computers running Mac OS 10.7,
    Windows 7, or Ubuntu Linux. It also has several specialty stations, including a digital video
    workstation and an audio workstation. Student techs and Academic Computing staff are available
    to assist with computing questions and needs.</p>
   <h3>Computer Applications Lab (the CAL)</h3>
   <p>The home of Scientific Computing at Evergreen, the CAL supports students enrolled in the
    physical and natural sciences. Each of its two teaching labs contains 26 workstations.</p>
   <h3>PLATO Technology and Lecture Series Grants</h3>
   <p>Royalties received from the PLATO computer-aided instruction materials developed at Evergreen
    support technology grants and an annual lecture series on computer-related topics. The Lecture
    Series (a.k.a. Cutting Edge Symposium) supports an annual guest speaker series on computers and
    technology. Some past themes include computers in the arts, software engineering, artificial
    intelligence, and the Internet.&#160; Technology grants support projects that strengthen and
    enhance curriculum incorporating the use of computer technology.</p>
   <h3>Robotics</h3>
   <p>Evergreen offers students a collection of tools to make robots, including Arduino
    microcontrollers, Scribblers, and iRobots.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <iframe width="560" height="315" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0"
     src="//www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/uDwN-Lrcg1I?rel=0"/>
    <p class="caption">In this video, the director of the QuaSR center talks about the tutoring
     available on-site at QuaSR, and how QuaSR is reaching out to other programs.</p>
   </div>
   <h3>The QuaSR Center</h3>
   <p>Evergreen&#8217;s QuaSR (Quantitative and Symbolic Reasoning) Center provides a supportive
    space for students who need assistance in math, economics, biology, chemistry, physics,
    statistics, music reading, and anything else scientific or mathematical. During the school year,
    drop-in tutoring is available six days a week. Many students use the QuaSR Center to do homework
    and get occasional help when they need it. Others come for more individual help or to work in
    small groups. The center&#8217;s student tutors have demonstrated expertise in the subjects they
    teach.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>Computer Science Foundations</h3>
   <p>
    <em>
     <small>Offered Fall 2017&#8211;Winter 2018</small>
    </em>
   </p>
   <p>In this program, students learn the intellectual concepts and skills that are essential for
    advanced work in computer science and beneficial for computing work in support of other
    disciplines. Students will have the opportunity to achieve a deeper understanding of
    increasingly complex computing systems by acquiring knowledge and skills in mathematical
    abstraction, problem solving, and the organization and analysis of hardware and software
    systems. The program covers material such as algorithms, data structures, computer organization
    and architecture, logic, discrete mathematics, and programming in the context of the liberal
    arts.</p>
   <p>We will explore our curriculum by way of lectures, programming labs, workshops, and
    seminars.</p>
   <p>
    <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/computersciencefoundations-16116"
     >View this program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="A student learns HTML" class="image-full" src="images/computer-science/web-design.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Faculty Richard Weiss works with students learning HTML in the summer web
     design class in the computer lab.</p>
   </div>
  </sample>
  <projects/>
  <facultybios>
   <p><strong>Neal Nelson</strong> has worked as an applications engineer, a senior design engineer,
    a software engineer, and a software developer in industry and academia. His research and
    academic interests include formal languages, programming language design, functional languages,
    type theory, operating systems, and computer architecture and logic design. His teaching
    interests include the construction of project-based implementations designed to expose students
    to advanced and abstract material in formal languages, programming language design, and
    operating systems design and implementation. He holds a B.A. in mathematics from Washington
    State University, an M.S. in computer science from Washington State University, and a Ph.D. in
    computer science from the Oregon Graduate Institute, now the Oregon Health Science
    University.</p>
   <p><strong>Sherri Shulman</strong> has worked as a software developer and researcher in industry
    and academia. Her research and academic interests include formal languages, logic, programming
    language design and semantics, type theory, and operating systems. Her teaching interests
    include the construction of project-based implementations designed to expose students to
    advanced and abstract material in formal languages, programming language design, and operating
    systems design and implementation. She holds a B.A. in natural science from Shimer College, an
    M.S. in computer science from the Illinois Institute of Technology, and a Ph.D. in computer
    science from the Oregon Graduate Institute, now the Oregon Health Science University.</p>
   <p><strong>Richard Weiss</strong> specializes in computer security, computer vision, robotics,
    and computer architecture. His research includes protecting smartphone personal data. In
    computer vision, he has applied differential geometry to constructing 3-D models of curved
    surfaces from multiple images. His teaching interests incorporate mathematics and computer
    science with music, art, linguistics, and cognitive science. He has a National Science
    Foundation grant to develop educational cybersecurity games. He earned an A.B in mathematics
    from Brandeis University, a Ph.D. in mathematics from Harvard University, and has worked as a
    software engineer.</p>
  </facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/environmental-studies</url>
  <title>Environmental Studies</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:06</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T10:42:58</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode>Environmental Studies/Agriculture</directorycode>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Raft down the Grand Canyon. Shape environmental legislation. Climb the slopes of
    Mount Rainier. Collect algae in the Puget Sound. Survey the giant forests of the Pacific
    Northwest.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <a class="lazy-load" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GhZp-4gIsBA">
     <img alt="" src="images/environmental-studies/yellowstone-trip-2012.jpg"/>
    </a>
    <p class="caption">Students visit Yellowstone National Park for the program Environmental
     Analysis to study the unique geological and microbiotic conditions in the park.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Getting out in the field is easy when you have the field right outside the classroom. Students
    in environmental studies benefit from Evergreen&#8217;s <a href="#resources">natural learning
     labs</a>: our 1,000-acre rain forest, open shoreline, and organic farm. Our location in
    Washington&#8217;s capital city makes getting involved in environmental politics easy. Students
    live and learn where policies are created. The surrounding community&#8217;s high level of
    environmental consciousness and the Pacific Northwest&#8217;s cultural and natural heritage form
    an unparalleled backdrop to your studies.</p>
   <p>Environmental studies offers introductory and advanced work in a wide array of laboratory and
    field studies that incorporate social sciences, environmental justice, biology, geology,
    chemistry, climatology, evolution, ecology, hydrology, and oceanography. You can also work
    independently with support through <a
     href="http://www.evergreen.edu/individualstudy/individuallearningcontracts">independent
     contracts</a>, internships, and research. You&#8217;ll have the opportunity to work along with
    faculty in real-world research, publish papers, attend conferences, and develop new techniques
    to answer novel questions. The mixture of an interdisciplinary approach and hands-on research
    allows you to make a transformative impact.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world.</strong></p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="" class="illus-full" src="images/environmental-studies/yellowstone-map.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Ken Tabbutt talks about the geological structure of the cliffs in Yellowstone
     as Andy Brabban and Clyde Barlow hold a geological map. Due to Evergreen&#8217;s emphasis on
     interdisciplinary learning, you&#8217;ll experience many programs taught by multiple
     faculty.</p>
   </div>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <p>Evergreen graduates with an emphasis in environmental studies prepares you for graduate
    studies and careers in the field. Our graduates are leaders in ecology, environmental health,
    natural resource management, conservation, forestry, wildlife biology, politics, economics, and
    global sustainability movements.</p>
   <p>You also have the option of continuing your studies with our <a
     href="http://www.evergreen.edu/mes/">Master of Environmental Studies.</a></p>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="" class="image-full" src="images/environmental-studies/climate-change-lecture.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Christopher Sabine, director of the Pacific Marine Environmental Laboratory
     at the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), talks about the global carbon
     cycle, climate change, and ocean acidification.</p>
   </div>
   <h3>The Organic Farm</h3>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">Students of all levels have access to science labs with a full range of
     equipment and high-tech tools.</p>
   </div>
   <p>At <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/organicfarm">the Organic Farm</a> students can explore
    sustainable agriculture, agro-ecology, and environmental sciences. In addition to three acres of
    certified organic fields, the farm&#8217;s facilities include a food-grade laboratory, the
    student-designed and -built <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/organicfarm/farmhouse">Organic
     Farmhouse</a>, and the student-run <a
     href="http://www.evergreen.edu/organicfarm/demetersgarden">Demeter&#8217;s</a> permaculture
    demonstration site and <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/organicfarm/communitygarden">Community
     Gardens</a>.</p>
   <h3>The Evergreen State College Forest &amp; Campus Shoreline</h3>
   <p>Evergreen&#8217;s 1,000-acre forest is ideal for studying a lowland Puget Sound second-growth
    rainforest. Through the <a href="http://blogs.evergreen.edu/eeon/">Evergreen Ecological
     Observation Network</a> (EEON), students and faculty conduct long-term scientific research. The
    college&#8217;s 3,300-foot shoreline offers a variety of ecosystems and natural features for
    students to investigate.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="" class="illus-full"
     src="images/environmental-studies/environmental-analysis-chem-lab.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Students do a titrations lab in the program Environmental Analysis.</p>
   </div>
   <h3>Labs, Gardens, &amp; Collections</h3>
   <p>Students of all levels have access to science labs with a full range of equipment and
    high-tech tools. You can study some 27,000 specimens in the college&#8217;s zoological,
    botanical, and mycological collections. Evergreen&#8217;s campus is also dotted with a variety
    of teaching gardens.</p>
   <h3>Sustainability in Prisons Project</h3>
   <p>The <a href="http://sustainabilityinprisons.org">Sustainability in Prisons Project</a> trains
    inmates and correctional staff at local prisons to carry out ecological research and
    conservation projects.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <img alt="" class="illus-full" src="images/environmental-studies/picturing-plants.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">The program Picturing Plants went on a field trip to Mima Mounds Glacial
     Heritage Preserve to identify and draw native prairie plants.</p>
   </div>
   <h3>Rachel Carson Forum</h3>
   <p>Students in Evergreen&#8217;s Master of Environmental Studies program organize this annual
    event. Experts speak on environmental topics such as local sustainability and climate
    change.</p>
   <h3>Sustainability House</h3>
   <p>The Sustainability House is a living/learning option for returning and transfer students.
    Residents commit to an environmentally conscious lifestyle, social justice, sustainable
    agriculture and activism.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>Environmental Problem Solving</h3>
   <em>
    <small>Offered Winter 2018&#8211;Spring 2018</small>
   </em>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">The Pacific Northwest&#8217;s cultural and natural heritage form an
     unparalleled backdrop to your studies.</p>
   </div>
   <p>It is a common misconception in environmentalism that if you can educate people about a
    problem, they will automatically take steps to solve it. In reality, environmental problem
    solving is much more complex. It requires a good grasp of the ecological system involved, the
    structure of government, and public policy&#8212;as well as the ability to work effectively in
    groups.</p>
   <p>This program covers basic ecology, political science, economics, and statistics in order to
    provide students with the necessary background to understand environmental problems. We will
    look at ecosystem structure, community ecology, population biology, and some of the ways in
    which human activities impact ecological systems. In the political science component, students
    will learn about the structure of government at several levels and the interaction of federal,
    state, and local government. We will take advantage of the proximity of the state legislature by
    attending committee meetings and observing the legislative process firsthand.</p>
   <p>
    <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/environmentalproblemsolving-16349"
     >View this program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="" class="illus-full" src="images/environmental-studies/elwha-dam.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Students in Restoration Ecology and Freshwater Ecology take a field trip to
     the Elwha River to study the effects of the Elwha Dam and how nature is recovering after its
     removal.</p>
   </div>
  </sample>
  <projects>
   <ul class="text-list">
    <li>Nisqually River education project film, a watershed overview focusing on water testing as a
     vehicle to evaluate safe salmon habitat</li>
    <li>Saving the hemlocks: Using bioanalytical chemistry to understand plant-insect interactions
     and save a threatened species</li>
    <li>A cost-benefit analysis of the oyster industry in Willapa, Bay</li>
    <li>Investigating changes in nutrient concentration and relative composition as regulating
     factors for algal biomass and species composition during the spring bloom in Budd Inlet</li>
    <li>Exploring migratory connectivity in the calliope hummingbird through stable isotope analysis
     of tail feathers</li>
    <li>Pacific Northwest second-growth forest carbon dynamics and tree diversity</li>
   </ul>
  </projects>
  <facultybios>
   <p><strong>Gerardo Chin-Leo</strong> teaches undergraduate and graduate students, primarily in
    the area of marine science. He was named a National Academies Education Fellow for
    2012&#8211;13. His research interests include marine microbiology, the ecology of phytoplankton
    with a focus on harmful algal blooms, and the ecology of bacteria as they relate to marine food
    webs and in anoxic environments. He earned a Ph.D in biological oceanography at the University
    of Delaware, where he also completed an M.S. in marine studies. He also earned a B.A. in biology
    from Reed College.</p>
   <p><strong>Martha Rosemeyer</strong> teaches in the areas of ecological agriculture and food
    systems. Current research interests include creating a local sustainable food system and the
    science and culture of cooking. She has researched microbial ecology and nutrient cycling in
    traditional agricultural systems in Costa Rica and worked in reconciling nature and agriculture
    in the tropics and temperate Wisconsin. She earned her Ph.D. in biology from the University of
    California, Santa Cruz; M.S. in plant science from the University of Arizona; and B.S. in plant
    pathology from the University of Wisconsin-Madison.</p>
  </facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/history</url>
  <title>History</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:07</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T10:48:41</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode>History</directorycode>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Discover how people thought, lived, worked, played, loved, and struggled in the
    past. Puzzle over why societies, traditions, and ways of thinking change over time. Appreciate
    and interpret experiences of people around the globe from the ancient world to the present.
    Grasp the challenges of developing sound insights and understanding about the past.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Freedom Dreams" class="image-full" src="images/history/freedom-dreams.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>Faculty member Greg Mullins talks about the history of Capitol Lake during a tour of the
      downtown murals and the State Capitol. In the 1930s, the mudflats in front of the Capitol were
      home to a shanty community called Little Hollywood.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>Nobel Prize-winning American novelist William Faulkner wrote, &#8220;The past is never dead.
    It&#8217;s not even past.&#8221; At Evergreen historical study comes alive in conversation with
    the present and through collaboration with other fields.</p>
   <p>Students of history examine every dimension of the human experience &#8212; private life and
    politics, ideas and the material world, family and public institutions, identity and power,
    labor and leisure. Programs in history can include the study of literature, political science,
    economics, philosophy, Native American studies, environmental studies, the arts, and popular
    culture.</p>
   <div class="box supplement">
    <h2>Opportunities to Study</h2>
    <ul>
     <li>Social, cultural, and political history including gender, race, and sexuality</li>
     <li>Western Europe including Britain, France, and Ireland</li>
     <li>Eastern Europe and Russia</li>
     <li>United States, American indigenous peoples, and Latin America</li>
     <li>North Africa and the Middle East</li>
     <li>Southeast Asia including Indonesia</li>
     <li>Ancient Mediterranean cultures</li>
    </ul>
   </div>
   <p>Studying history promotes critical thinking about big questions &#8212; what has caused
    specific revolutions? What is the relationship between individual memory and history? How can
    artifacts help us understand people from the past? How can documents crafted by people in power
    reveal both the emergence of dominant cultures and be read subversively?<em><br/>
    </em></p>
   <p>Since there are no easy answers, college-level history is not primarily about memorizing facts
    but about making connections, interpreting, and discovering webs of meaning.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Ireland in History and Memory" class="image-full"
     src="images/history/ireland-light.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>A group of students present a show called Spaces for Women as an end-of-quarter project for
      the program Ireland in History and Memory. The project comprised music, poetry and two pieces
      of papercut art.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>When you look at different people and times, you'll consider how people's lives which seem
    inexplicable to us made complete sense to them, and how understanding and interpreting their
    experiences helps us make sense of our world. You&#8217;ll challenge your assumptions about how
    individuals and communities live and make meaning with knowledge.</p>
   <p>Students who study history at Evergreen develop a historical imagination and cultivate
    insights that link the present with the past and bring valuable awareness to the future.</p>
   <p>You'll prepare for professional work or graduate study by learning how to interpret evidence,
    create narratives about human experience, and develop sound arguments. You'll learn how
    historical knowledge is formed by creating it yourself, learning how to do historical research
    and interpreting what you encounter. You'll learn how to understand secondary sources, research
    archival materials, practice oral history methods, and shed light on the human experience by
    honing all these skills.</p>
   <p>The analytical, research, and writing skills developed by studying history provide strong
    preparation for many fields, both in history and related disciplines such as classics and
    archaeology, European studies, American studies, law, and creative writing.</p>
   <p>Evergreen graduates with a history background have gone on to careers as lawyers, college and
    public school teachers, librarians, archivists, museum professionals, journalists, fiction
    writers, and historians.</p>
   <div class="box supplement">
    <h2>In the News</h2>
    <p>
     <a
      href="http://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/how-an-evergreen-state-prof-guided-the-supreme-court/"
      >Evergreen history faculty guided the Supreme Court decision on gay marriage.</a>
    </p>
   </div>
   <p>Historical studies prepares students, whatever their professions, to be thoughtful and engaged
    members of their communities with the ability to appreciate difference, nuance, and context.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn't just change your life &#8212; it gives you the tools to
    change the world.</p>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <div class="box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p><strong>Leah Olson</strong>, class of 2013, is now in her second season at the American
     School&#8216;s Agora in Athens excavations. She studied classics, history, and archaeology
     while at Evergreen.</p>
   </div>
   <p>The analytical, research, and writing skills developed in the study of history are a strong
    preparation for many fields. Many have continued their education with advanced degrees, both in
    history and in related fields like classics and archaeology, European studies, American studies,
    and creative writing.</p>
   <p>Evergreen graduates with a history emphasis have gone on to careers as lawyers, teachers,
    librarians, archivists, museum professionals, journalists, and historians.</p>
   <p>Historical studies prepares students, whatever their profession, to be thoughtful and engaged
    members of their communities with the ability to appreciate difference, nuance, and context.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Cornell Box dioramas" class="image-full" src="images/history/cornell-box-dioramas.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>Students in Culture as History presented the Cornell Box dioramas they made for their winter
      quarter final project.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="A History of &#8220;Race&#8221;" class="image-full"
     src="images/history/history-of-race-class-meeting.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>Students in the program A History of &#8220;Race&#8221; in the U.S. meet in small groups in
      the alcove space on the ground floor of the Library building. The program encompasses African
      American studies, history, and political science.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <h3>The Library</h3>
   <p>Evergreen's collection is tailored to support your research with more than 400,000 items
    including article databases, books, periodicals, films, games, and more. Faculty librarians
    provide research assistance. You also have access to materials from libraries in the Pacific
    Northwest and from around the world. <a href="http://library.evergreen.edu/">Learn more about
     the library.</a></p>
   <h3>Washington State Archives</h3>
   <p>Students with an interest in Washington state history have convenient access to the state's
    main archive in downtown Olympia. State archives include papers of all governors and all
    official records of the state. Find out about the <a
     href="https://www.sos.wa.gov/archives/archives_state.aspx">Washington State Archives</a>.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <img alt="Culture as History" class="image-full" src="images/history/culture-as-history.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>Students create timelines in the Culture as History program.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <h3>Earth Dynamics</h3>
   <p>
    <em>
     <small>Offered Fall 2017&#8211;Winter 2018<br/>
     </small>
    </em>
   </p>
   <p>Human activity shapes the environment. Earth warmed out of the last ice age about 10,000 years
    ago, enabling our species to develop stable societies and transform the experience of being
    alive. Agricultural activity emitted greenhouse gases that changed Earth&#8217;s air, water, and
    land. People changed, too, improving technologies and creating written and artistic records of
    their ideas and histories. Today, we understand our impacts on the environment in ways
    incomprehensible to our ancestors, and we are challenged to mitigate those impacts with
    knowledge, skill, and political will.</p>
   <p>This program will examine changes in the Earth system, human understanding of those changes,
    and the history of technological efforts to enhance human flourishing and shape our impacts on
    the environment. We'll study multiple drivers of climate change such as Sun-Earth interactions,
    volcanoes, industry, consumption, and greenhouse gases. We&#8217;ll consider the changing role
    of science in providing the understanding required for people and planet to thrive together.</p>
   <p>
    <a
     href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/earthdynamicspeopleplacetechnologyandhistory-16001"
     >View this program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
  </sample>
  <projects>
   <p>Evergreen students presented papers at the annual Northwest Undergraduate Classics Conference
    at Willamette University in 2013 and 2015.</p>
   <ul>
    <li>Elizabeth Ferrington, 2013: &#8220;From Birth to Burial: Girls and the Control of Sexuality
     in Ancient Greece.&#8221;</li>
    <li>Allegra Radcliffe, 2013: &#8220;Midwifery and the Plebeian Woman in the Roman
     Empire.&#8221;&#160;Allegra is traveling to Greece this summer to present a paper on dance in
     the late 18th and early 19th century in Greece at the Messolonghi Byron society's annual
     conference.</li>
    <li>Alexander Witherspoon, 2015: &#8220;Hanno: an Inquiry and Commentary.&#8221; He was the only
     first-year student presenting at the conference.</li>
   </ul>
  </projects>
  <facultybios/>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/home</url>
  <title>Fields of Study</title>
  <created>2014-02-26T12:51:23</created>
  <changed>2015-06-30T15:58:58</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>simonsc</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode/>
  <intro/>
  <after/>
  <resources/>
  <sample/>
  <projects/>
  <facultybios/>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/home-old</url>
  <title>Fields of Study</title>
  <created>2015-02-25T10:55:57</created>
  <changed>2015-02-25T10:55:57</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>nelsone</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode/>
  <intro/>
  <after/>
  <resources/>
  <sample/>
  <projects/>
  <facultybios/>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/inventory</url>
  <title>Page Title</title>
  <created>2016-10-26T14:21:36</created>
  <changed>2016-10-26T14:22:35</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>nelsone</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode/>
  <intro/>
  <after/>
  <resources/>
  <sample/>
  <projects/>
  <facultybios/>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/native-studies</url>
  <title>Native American and Indigenous Studies</title>
  <created>2015-07-23T08:44:51</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T12:04:10</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode/>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Focus on the vitality and diversity of Native nations and the value of
    indigenous knowledge. Study the effects of European-American social values and structures on
    Native history and contemporary life. Examine global effects of colonialism and treaty
    relationships between tribal nations and settler governments.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Woodcarving studio" class="image-full"
     src="images/native-american-studies/woodcarving-studio.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>The first building in The Longhouse&#8217;s indigenous arts campus efforts is a carving
      studio in the shape of a replica longhouse.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>Native American and Indigenous Studies at Evergreen is an interdisciplinary field that
    examines the histories, cultures, politics, and contemporary experiences of Indigenous peoples
    in the Northwest and beyond. Founded upon visionary leadership and long-term relationships
    between Pacific Northwest tribes and Evergreen, programs in Native studies embrace indigenous
    knowledge as a field of multidisciplinary study. Faculty develop culturally relevant curriculum
    that strengthens the college's connection to indigenous peoples of the United States, Canada,
    Aotearoa, and the Pacific Rim. Classes take place both on the Olympia campus and at area tribal
    centers where Evergreen&#8217;s Reservation-Based Community-Determined programs are offered.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Paddle to Squaxin" class="image-full"
     src="images/native-american-studies/paddle-to-squaxin.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>The Evergreen State College Longhouse partnered with the Squaxin Museum to host the Paddle
      to Squaxin Tribal Journey in 2012.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>As you learn about Native studies, you will get experience combining theory with
    practice.&#160;Learn from indigenous Pacific Rim artists in the Longhouse&#8217;s carving
    studio. Explore the canoe as transportation, cultural artifact, and symbol of sovereignty and
    nation-building through a tribal canoe journey. Learn issues of tribal governance, economic
    sustainability, and self-determination from tribal leaders and policy makers.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world</strong>.</p>
   <aside class="box pull-box">
    <p class="pull-quote">Truly interdisciplinary, Native studies supports students in developing
     and strengthening quality skills in analysis, research, writing, and oral communication in
     their chosen fields.</p>
   </aside>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <aside class="box pull-box supplement">
    <p class="pull-quote">Consider continuing your education at the only MPA tribal governance
     concentration in the country.</p>
   </aside>
   <p>A truly interdisciplinary degree, Native American studies supports students in developing and
    strengthening quality skills in analysis, research, writing, and oral communication in their
    chosen fields. Many pursue graduate studies, and most work in tribal communities. Our graduates
    have chosen careers in tribal law, health, and government, including teaching in tribal schools,
    working on tribal policy, and administrative work</p>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <h3>&#8220;House of Welcome&#8221; Longhouse Education and Cultural Center</h3>
   <p>A gathering place for indigenous arts and cultures through education, cultural preservation,
    creative expression, and economic development. Participate in multicultural classes,
    presentations, performances, and more. Meet Native artists and visit exhibitions and art sales
    throughout the year, including the annual winter holiday arts and crafts fair.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="The Longhouse interior" class="image-full"
     src="images/native-american-studies/longhouse-interior.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>Participate in multicultural classes, presentations, performances, and more at The
      Longhouse.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>Indigenous Pacific Rim artists-in-residence teach and practice in the Longhouse&#8217;s
    carving studio. In 2017, a new fiber arts studio will open as another step towards an Indigenous
    Arts Campus where the art-making facilities and the surrounding campus are based on indigenous
    architectural design and cultural concepts.</p>
   <p>Discover the full range of activities at <a href="http://evergreen.edu/longhouse">The
     Longhouse</a>.</p>
   <h3>Tribal Reservation-Based Community-Determined Programs</h3>
   <p>For place-bound students who are deeply connected to tribal communities. Classes take place on
    Indian reservations in western Washington. &#8220;Community determined&#8221; means the program
    is initiated at the tribes&#8217; request, a tribal advisory board provides curricular
    direction, and that program content addresses significant community issues and uses community
    resources. Students attend weekly classes at reservation sites and also attend Saturday classes
    at the Longhouse, where all students come together for classes, workshops, and cultural events.
     <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/tribal/">Explore the Reservation-Based Community-Determined
     Program.</a></p>
   <h3>Master of Public Administration in Tribal Governance</h3>
   <p>Consider continuing your education at the only MPA tribal governance concentration in the
    country. We provide current and future tribal leaders with the knowledge and skills needed to
    work successfully in Indian Country. The degree prepares students for a wide range of jobs in
    tribal, federal, state, and local governments, and nonprofits. Learn more about <a
     href="../mpa/home.htm">the MPA program</a>.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>Speaking Truth in 20th- and 21st-Century Indigenous Arts: Legacy, Defiance, and Agency</h3>
   <p>
    <em>Offered Winter 2018&#8211;Spring 2018</em>
   </p>
   <p>In this program, we will critically examine some of the colonizing aspects of U.S./Native
    history, anthropology, and the tourist industry that motivated many mid-20th and early
    21st-century indigenous artists to &#8220;speak truth&#8221; through paintings, sculptures,
    carvings, basketry, bead work, photography, prints, performance, and multimedia installations as
    a means of maintaining and defending Native identity and tribal sovereignty.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="An artist works on her print" class="image-full"
     src="images/native-american-studies/printmaking.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>An artist carves a design into leather. When she is finished, it will be covered in ink and
      used to create printed design pieces.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>Through lectures, films, readings by indigenous scholars and writers, student-led seminars,
    guest speakers, weekly studio or research workshops, and field trips to mainstream and tribal
    museums, students will critically reflect on the power, meaning, and contributions of
    contemporary Native art, not only to indigenous people, but to the non-Native world. Students
    will develop skills as writers, artists, researchers, and potential allies by studying
    indigenous scholarship and the artworks of indigenous artists from the 20th and 21st centuries,
    and by developing research papers and presentations.</p>
   <p>
    <a
     href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/speakingtruthin20thand21stcenturyindigenousartslegacydefianceandagency-16438"
     >View this program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
   <figure class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Students taking turns speaking at a microphone" class="image-full"
     src="images/native-american-studies/reservation-based-battlegrounds.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>Students in the program Tribal: Reservation Based Community Determined break into small
      groups to talk about challenges and opportunities for Native American health care. The session
      was part of regular classes known as Battlegrounds, which draw together students from eight
      regional reservations that participate in the program.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
  </sample>
  <projects/>
  <facultybios>
   <p><strong>Zoltan Grossman</strong> teaches Native American studies with an emphasis on global
    ethnic relations and world indigenous peoples. His expertise also includes U.S. race relations,
    environmental justice and movements, maps and historical cartography, globalization, and
    military interventions. He earned a Ph.D in geography in 2002, an M.S. in geography in 1998, and
    a B.A. and B.S. in history and geography in 1984, all from the University of Wisconsin.</p>
   <p><strong>Frances V. Rains</strong> teaches Native American studies with an emphasis on
    education, history, and women&#8217;s studies. Her expertise includes indigenous knowledge,
    decolonization, indigenous sustainability, critical race theory, and qualitative research
    methods. She earned a Ph.D in curriculum and instruction/curriculum theory/multicultural
    education-elementary education in 1995, an M.S. in elementary education/mathematics in 1987, and
    a B.S. in elementary education/American Indian education in 1978, all from Indiana
    University.</p>
   <p><strong>Gail Tremblay</strong> is of Onondaga and Micmac ancestry. She teaches Native American
    studies with an emphasis on the visual arts, creative writing, and poetry. &#160;A prolific
    author and internationally exhibited artist, her expertise includes art, weaving, art history,
    contemporary Native American literature, poetry, literature, multicultural literature, and
    diversity and gender equity in art education. She earned an MFA in English (poetry) from the
    University of Oregon in 1969, and a B.A. in drama from the University of New Hampshire in
    1967.</p>
  </facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/performing-arts</url>
  <title>Performing Arts</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:07</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T11:02:11</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode>Performing Arts</directorycode>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Compose&#160;and&#160;produce&#160;original music and dance works.
    Explore&#160;the work of established playwrights, composers, and
    choreographers.&#160;Perform&#160;in music, theater, and dance
    productions.&#160;Design&#160;sets, costumes, lighting, and sound for shows
    you&#160;present&#160;to audiences on campus and off.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Machinal" class="image-full" src="images/performing-arts/machinal.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Theater Intensive production of <em>Machinal</em> by Sophie Tredwell.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Studying the performing arts at Evergreen enables you to combine your passion for your
    discipline with the discovery and articulation of your desires. You'll learn about the larger
    social world the arts inhabit and reach out to explore and create the possible but not yet
    existing realities that the arts can reveal.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Bodies and Music in Motion" class="image-full"
     src="images/performing-arts/bodies-and-music-in-motion-singing.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">The students of Bodies and Music in Motion host an end-of-quarter performance
     in the Communications Building dance studio. The performance included music, singing, dance,
     and poetry.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Our performing arts students have done wonderful work in experimental and traditional spheres.
    They&#8217;ve directed plays by Shakespeare, Brecht, and others. They've written and performed
    in avante-garde operas with self-built and designed musical instruments. And they've and created
    and danced in productions for the campus and larger community. At Evergreen, students learn
    about the technologies of theater and musical sound synthesis and they participate in music,
    theater, and dance performances under faculty direction. In our multidisciplinary classes,
    you&#8217;ll have the opportunity to work in groups that combine all the facets of performing
    arts to produce rewarding work.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world</strong>.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Bodies and Music in Motion" class="image-full"
     src="images/performing-arts/bodies-and-music-in-motion-dance3.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">The performing arts curriculum is supported by a wide range of specialized
     facilities for students to explore a variety of expressive styles.</p>
   </div>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">At Evergreen, students learn about the technologies of theater and musical
     sound synthesis and they participate in music, theater, and dance performances under faculty
     direction.</p>
   </div>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <p>Our graduates have gone on to graduate studies in drama, music composition, ethnomusicology,
    and more. They&#8217;ve found work with dance companies and theater groups in New York and
    beyond. Many have gone on to professional work in their chosen fields. Our interdisciplinary
    outlook allows students to follow their passions while broadening their horizons.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="The Vagina Monologues" class="image-full"
     src="images/performing-arts/vagina-monologues.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Backstage at the 2013 performance of <em>The Vagina Monologues</em> by Eve
     Ensler at the Evergreen State College. The show, now it's 11th year at the college, is
     presented by the Evergreen Womyn&#8217;s Resource Center.</p>
   </div>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <h3>Labs for Film, Animation, Music Technology, &amp; Design</h3>
   <p>Created for use by students of the performing and media arts, the Design Lab boasts 50
    workstations and a variety of equipment including light tables, drafting tables, tables with
    cutting mats, and animation stations suitable for 2-D and 3-D creation. This space is also
    equipped with full audio and video playback equipment and art critique or presentation area.</p>
   <h3>Performance Spaces</h3>
   <p>The Experimental Theater is a fully equipped black box theater with flexible seating and
    staging. The theater can seat up to 200. There is a counterweight system to accommodate flown
    scenery, lighting and soft goods. It is equipped with new dimmers and lighting console, as well
    as full sound and video support.</p>
   <p>The Recital Hall is a space acoustically designed for music recitals. It is also used for
    drama, dance, film and lecture presentations. It seats 200, has a state of the art lighting
    system, and 7.1 surround sound. The room has a large projection screen, playback system, and
    audio recording facility.</p>
   <p>The newly remodeled Dance Studio has a world-class sprung wood floor and ample wall-mounted
    mirrors that can easily accommodate up to 75 dancers. It has a fixed lighting grid and features
    a full audio and video playback system. The space can be configured for performance, and can
    hold an audience of up to 50 people.</p>
   <p>The newly added and exceptionally flexible Performance Studio was designed as a mini black box
    style space with fixed lighting grid and wall-mounted mirrors. It is ideal for small student-run
    productions and can seat up to 60 audience members.</p>
   <p>The Mini Experimental Theater (M.E.T.) is another mini black box style space, ideal for
    workshops and is equipped with a lighting grid, and moveable sound and video equipment. This
    space can be configured for small performances and is well suited for student-run
    productions.</p>
   <h3>Production Spaces</h3>
   <p>The Performance and Production Studio is a multi-use space, seating up to 150 students. It
    features exceptional acoustics and has an adjacent audio control room, a moderate stage space,
    and three shallow stepped risers accommodating lectures, rehearsals, audio recording and
    performance.</p>
   <p>Located next to our cutting-edge Multitrack Studio the Music Performance and Rehearsal space
    allows for advanced audio recording and post-production. Variable sound dampening makes this
    room ideal for a variety of musical styles in addition to other types of presentations to a live
    audience of up to 50. This room features full audio and video playback.</p>
   <p>The Scene Shop is equipped with wood, metal and paint departments and staffed by students
    whose work supports academic productions through a variety of disciplines, including stage
    management, design, carpentry, lighting, painting and costuming. The costume shop is equipped
    with several standard and industrial sewing machines, sergers, and a dye and laundry facility.
    The shop also houses the college&#8217;s stock of set pieces, props and costumes for student
    check out.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>Making a Living and a Life</h3>
   <p>
    <em>
     <small>Offered at Fall 2017&#8211;Spring 2018<br/>
     </small>
    </em>
   </p>
   <dl class="program-description">
    <dd>
     <p>This program is for students who want to make a sustainable living through a creative
      practice, products, or services. This includes students in the arts, entertainment,
      communications, business, social change, food production, and other fields. Our aim is to help
      you become a social entrepreneur equipped for a career in either for-profit or nonprofit
      organizations.</p>
     <p>We will look closely at the history and theory of work, particularly in the areas of
      organizational management and change. Workplaces are changing, becoming more diverse, varied,
      and globalized. Keeping this in mind, we will also look closely at the internal infrastructure
      of organizations and learn about planning and development, writing business plans, doing
      organizational and marketing research, analyzing data using statistics, and creating budgets
      using spreadsheet programs. Small-group projects will bring students together to create
      commentaries on our texts and themes via visual arts, creative writing, and performance.
      In-program salons will offer opportunities for artists to share their work-in-progress and for
      artisans, crafters, food producers, and social entrepreneurs to share their prototypes.</p>
     <p>
      <a
       href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/makingalivingandalifesustainablecreativepractice-16359"
       >View this program in the catalog.</a>
     </p>
    </dd>
   </dl>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Beggar&#8217;s Opera" class="image-full"
     src="images/performing-arts/beggars-opera.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Eric Jacobs at a fitting for <em>The Beggar&#8217;s Opera</em> in the Costume
     Shop. Jacobs plays Macheath in a production staged by the program Musical Theater in Cultural
     Context.</p>
   </div>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement">
    <p class="pull-quote">You&#8217;ll learn about the larger social world the arts inhabit and
     reach out to explore and create the possible but not yet existing realities that the arts can
     reveal.</p>
   </div>
  </sample>
  <projects/>
  <facultybios>
   <p><strong>Sean Williams</strong> lives and breathes music. She teaches ethnomusicology, the
    study of music in cultural context. She plays more than 30 musical instruments and has traveled
    to&#8212;and lived in&#8212;many parts of the world. Her latest book, <em>Bright Star of the
     West: Joe Heaney, Irish Song Man</em>, recently won a top ethnomusicology award. Her work
    focuses on the many ways in which music and culture intersect through spirituality,
    urbanization, food, immigration, gender, language, and politics.</p>
   <p><strong>Kabby Mitchell III</strong> was born to dance, and he delights in sharing his plethora
    of experiences from dancing with the Dance Theatre of Harlem, Nederlands Dans Theater, and
    Pacific Northwest Ballet. His teaching practices&#8212;through example and
    choreography&#8212;have impacted diverse communities globally. He believes that dance is a
    language that can speak to all involved and he is excited by the infinite possibilities when
    co-learners find their voices through movement exploration and intellectual curiosity.</p>
   <p><strong>Rose Jang</strong> combines her cultural familiarity of Chinese theater with training
    in Western theater. She is most interested in creating a continuum of understanding and
    application with her students to incorporate both the Asian sense of control and the Western
    predilection for creativity and individual freedom in the arts. She enjoys producing innovative
    shows in classical and experimental formats within multi-quarter programs, starting with serious
    pursuits of disciplines in both cerebral and kinesthetic aspects of theater arts.</p>
  </facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/political-economy-science</url>
  <title>Political Economy &amp; Political Science</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:06</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T12:08:28</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode/>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Examine the causes of social inequality. Explore connections between politics,
    economics, and popular culture. Develop an historically-grounded global perspective. Envision
    alternative economic systems and study the history of movements for change.<strong><br/>
    </strong></p>
   <figure class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Thomas Herndon speaks in the CCAM television studio" class="image-full"
     src="images/political-economy-science/herndon-CCAM.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>Evergreen alumnus Thomas Herndon is interviewed by Professor Emeritus of Political Economy
      Alan Nasser in the CCAM studio. Herndon made headlines when he found errors in the data set
      used by pro-austerity Harvard economists Carmen Reinhart and Kenneth Rogoff.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>Political economy is an interdisciplinary field combining economics, history, politics,
    sociology, and philosophy. It asks who has what, who does what kinds of work, how did it get to
    be that way, and how it could be different. Political science deals with systems of government,
    and the analysis of political activity and behavior. While there is overlap, political
    economists focus on economic processes, their relation to power and public policy, and their
    influence on people's lives and social institutions while political scientists focus on the
    study of governments and how they work.</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Tomorrow Today program" class="image-full"
     src="images/political-economy-science/political-economy-tomorrow-today.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>Students learn the process of planning and pitching ideas for short films in the program
      Tomorrow Today: Political Economy and Culture of the Future.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>At Evergreen, you can study the history of empires past and present in structuring the global
    economy. You can examine food systems and agriculture in the U.S. and internationally. You can
    look at the role mass media plays in our social relationships.</p>
   <p>You can analyze the relation between capitalism and race, gender and class inequalities, and
    how these inequalities can be changed by creating liberatory alternatives to
    capitalism.&#160;</p>
   <p>You can learn how social change has occurred in the past so you can join with others as more
    effective agents of change. You can apply your learning through internships and research.
    Finally, you can explore alternative visions for economies and societies that promote justice
    and environmental sustainability.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world.</strong></p>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <div class="box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <div class="media media-column">
     <div class="media-img">
      <p>
       <img alt="Thomas Herndon" class="image-full"
        src="images/political-economy-science/herndon.jpg"/>
      </p>
     </div>
     <div class="media-body">
      <p><strong>Thomas Herndon '07</strong>&#160; weakened the case for austerity policies
       worldwide by successfully challenging the influential work of two Harvard economists.
       Economists, news outlets, and political groups across the U.S. and around the world cited his
       work, landing Herndon an appearance on the Colbert Report. He is a graduate student in
       economics at the University of Massachusetts Amherst.</p>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Popular Uprisings program" class="image-full"
     src="images/political-economy-science/popular-uprisings-outdoor-seminar.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>The program Popular Uprisings: 1968, 2011 and the Road Forward combines political and
      economic studies with sociology and history. Faculty Elizabeth Williamson holds seminar on the
      roof of Sem II with a group of students in the program.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>The skills in analysis, research, and writing developed through the study of political economy
    and political science are key preparation for work, future study, and meaningful participation
    in society.</p>
   <p>Many graduates have continued their education by earning advanced degrees in political
    economy, political science, economics, history, sociology, law, public policy, and related
    disciplines.</p>
   <p>And Evergreen graduates with a political economy or political science background have gone on
    to careers in areas such as international relations, economics, journalism, teaching, labor and
    community organizing, human rights and global justice, social work, public policy, law, and
    public health.</p>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <h3>The Library</h3>
   <p>An intellectual hub on campus with study spaces and more than 400,000 items to support your
    research, including article databases, books, periodicals, films, games, and more. Faculty
    librarians provide research assistance. You also have access to materials from libraries in the
    Pacific Northwest and around the world. <a href="../library/home.htm">Learn more about the
     library.</a></p>
   <h3>Center for Community-Based Learning and Action</h3>
   <p>CCBLA links you with community organizations working on a wide range of issues. Services
    include a bulletin board with current opportunities for community involvement, a reference
    library on key approaches to community work including grantwriting, ethnography, community
    organizing, and information about Students In Service, an Americorps program that rewards
    students performing community service with tuition awards.</p>
   <h3>Gateways for Incarcerated Youth</h3>
   <p>Serve as an academic mentor and coach while Evergreen faculty lead seminars at juvenile
    correctional facilities. Gateways provides the individualized approach needed to reengage
    incarcerated youth in learning and community. Our focus on culture &#8212; helping all students
    learn their own and respecting others &#8212; is critical to breaking the cycle of
    incarceration, violence, and recidivism.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>Political Economy and Social Movements</h3>
   <p>
    <em>Offered Fall 2017&#8211;Winter 2018<br/>
    </em>
   </p>
   <p>What do we need to know in order to understand the fundamental economic, political, and social
    forces that shape our world, and how can we participate effectively in shaping those forces?</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Northwest Developments program" class="image-full"
     src="images/political-economy-science/city-council-meeting.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>In the program Northwest Developments: Land Use, Economics and the Politics of Growth,
      students enact a mock city council meeting to discuss a fictional development project in
      Seattle.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>This program is the primary gateway to the study of political economy at Evergreen. It
    introduces students to the building blocks of political-economic analysis: the history and
    institutions of capitalism, mainstream and alternative economic frameworks, theories of
    democracy, and theories of social change. We add to this a study of social movements in the past
    and present, looking at persuasive goals in relation to economic and political conditions, and
    learning about methods of influencing public attitudes and institutional policies</p>
   <figure class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Reslient Communities program" class="image-full"
     src="images/political-economy-science/resilient-communities.jpg"/>
    <figcaption>
     <p>Students will expand their capacity to engage in public debate and social-justice organizing
      by building skills in democratic decision-making, critical thinking, economic analysis,
      writing, researching, public speaking, media production, and quantitative methods.</p>
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
   <p>
    <a
     href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/politicaleconomyandsocialmovements-16739"
     >View this program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
  </sample>
  <projects>
   <ul>
    <li>Tracing Fictitious Capital of Land: Enclosures, Ownership in Question, and the Transition to
     Capitalism</li>
    <li>The Role of Argentina in the Global Beef trade, 1870-1920: A Food Regime Analysis</li>
    <li>Gendered (Re)Production and the Neoliberal Regime: Women's Labor in Mexico, 1982-2000</li>
    <li>World cities in the Global South: Johannesburg and Bangkok</li>
    <li>Uneven Development during the Long Twentieth Century: A World-Systems Perspective with
     special reference to India (senior thesis)</li>
    <li>Keeping Capitalism Alive: Accumulation, Reinvestment and the Growing Costs</li>
   </ul>
  </projects>
  <facultybios>
   <p><strong>Peter Bohmer</strong> teaches political economy and economics at the Evergreen State
    College. His research and teaching interests include the political economy of racism, alternate
    economic systems,&#160; Latin American political economy including Venezuela and Cuba, the U.S.
    economy, labor studies, social movements&#160; and Marxism. He has been active in social
    movements since 1967. He has a B.S. in Economics with a minor in Math from M.I.T., and an M.A.
    and Ph.D. in Economics from the University of Massachusetts in Amherst.</p>
   <p><strong>Savvina Chowdhury</strong> teaches feminist economics, economics, and political
    economy. Her research interests include Muslim immigrant women. She earned her Ph.D. in 2005 in
    economics from the University of California, Riverside where she also earned her M.A. in
    economics. Her B.A. is in international studies, which she earned from the University of
    Southern Maine in 1995.</p>
   <p><strong>Steve Niva</strong> teaches international relations, political science, and Middle
    East studies. His research interests include U.S. foreign policy, alternatives to globalization,
    Israeli-Palestinian conflict, political philosophy, and social and political organizing. He
    earned his Ph.D. in political science (international relations and Middle East studies) from
    Columbia University in 1999 and his B.A. in government and international affairs from the
    University of Virginia in 1988.</p>
  </facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/psychology</url>
  <title>Psychology</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:06</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T11:13:35</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode/>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Delve into the intricacies of the human mind. Find out what makes people tick.
    Learn how to help people dealing with stress and addiction. Prepare for law school. Help people
    create their own path to successful living.</p>
   <img alt="Freeman Clinical Psychology Discussion" class="illus"
    src="images/clinical-psychology-discussion.jpg"/>
   <p>If you are fascinated by human behavior&#8212;how people think, feel, and
    act&#8212;Evergreen&#8217;s interdisciplinary approach to psychology offers a range of
    approaches for you to build your understanding of the social, psychological, and biological
    forces that influence human health and behavior.</p>
   <p>Evergreen will prepare you in both theory and practice for graduate study and work in clinical
    psychology, human and social services, and psychological research. Having a solid understanding
    of human behavior is an extremely marketable skill in a number of career settings including
    social services, advertising, marketing, education, health care, and politics.</p>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">If you&#8217;ve ever dreamed of making a real difference in other
     people&#8217;s lives, studying psychology can be a great way to achieve that goal.</p>
   </div>
   <p>At Evergreen, you&#8217;ll learn how to critically evaluate theories of human behavior and
    explore research methods that will further your understanding. You&#8217;ll be encouraged to
    explore psychology from multiple perspectives, integrating a range of approaches from which to
    consider human behavior, emotion, and thinking. You&#8217;ll study the history and systems of
    psychology, learn quantitative and qualitative research methods, and examine multicultural
    themes regarding race, gender, sexual orientation, class, religious identity, and
    ability/disability. Regionally-based internships in counseling and social services offer ample
    opportunities to gain experience in the field.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong>&#65279;
    &#8212; it gives you the tools to <strong>change the world</strong>.</p>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <div class="box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <div class="media media-column">
     <div class="media-img">
      <p>
       <a href="../magazine/2015spring-summer/protecting-adolescents-from-suicide.htm">
        <img alt="Portrait of Guy Diamond" class="image-full"
         src="images/psychology/guy-diamond.jpg"/>
       </a>
      </p>
     </div>
     <div class="media-body">
      <p><strong>Guy Diamond</strong>, class of 1981, has developed groundbreaking screening and
       family therapy techniques to reduce the risk of suicide in adolescents. <a
        href="../magazine/2015spring-summer/protecting-adolescents-from-suicide.htm">Find out
        more.</a></p>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <p>Psychology studies offer an enormous variety of career paths. The demand for psychological
    services in schools, hospitals, substance abuse treatment centers, and social services agencies
    continues to grow. Evergreen students are encouraged to extend their knowledge of psychology to
    other disciplines. Some go on to pursue graduate study in clinical, developmental, or cognitive
    psychology, counseling, or social work while others use psychological perspectives to inform
    their work in literature, the arts, and other fields. If you&#8217;ve ever dreamed of making a
    real difference in other people&#8217;s lives, studying psychology can be a great way to achieve
    that goal.</p>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <h3>The Evergreen Psychological Society</h3>
   <p>This student group is dedicated to providing space and resources for Evergreen students who
    are interested in psychology and the mind. Weekly meetings are held for discussion of
    psychology, information sharing, and networking opportunities with other psych students.</p>
   <img alt="Awakening in procession" class="image" src="images/awakening-in-procession.jpg"/>
   <h3>Internships and Research</h3>
   <p>Numerous internship opportunities in counseling and clinical settings, social service
    agencies, and schools are available for students interested in clinical psychology or
    counseling. Upper-level students may also work with faculty to conduct individual research
    projects in psychology or social sciences.</p>
   <h3>Western Psychological Association Convention</h3>
   <p>The Western Psychological Association (WPA) is the regional arm of the American Psychological
    Association. Their annual convention of psychology professionals and students allows students to
    explore the range of activities and topics that psychology offers, and to learn cutting edge
    research in the field. Faculty facilitate the trip annually for students who are interested in
    attending.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>Moving Toward Health</h3>
   <p>
    <small>
     <em>Offered Fall 2017&#8211;Winter 2018</em>
    </small>
   </p>
   <p>This program explores cultural determinants of health for communities and individuals through
    cross-cultural and mind-body perspectives. How can cultural practices become an integral part of
    prevention and education in promoting health in culturally respectful ways? How can we engage in
    transformational conversations about the connections between personal, community, and planetary
    health? Throughout the program, we will recognize that our individual choices can help us create
    both personal health and a sustainable environment, a conscious life and a positive presence in
    society.</p>
   <p>Students will have an opportunity to learn in many ways, using diverse modalities, including
    working with multiple intelligences and mindfulness practices. We will integrate somatic
    learning into our studies, including movement, qigong (a Chinese system of physical exercises
    and breathing control), and expressive arts workshops. Our inquiry will ask us to attune
    ourselves to the wisdom that is available and present in our mind-body awareness. We will
    participate in community readings, community service, rigorous writing assignments, and critical
    study of important texts.</p>
   <p>
    <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/movingtowardhealth-16418">View this
     program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
   <p>
    <img alt="Freeman Clinical Psychology" class="illus"
     src="images/freeman-clinical-psychology.jpg"/>
   </p>
  </sample>
  <projects>
   <ul class="text-list">
    <li>What factors and issues impede immigrant mothers from the former Soviet Union from using
     educational resources?</li>
    <li>Early childhood development in rural Kenya: A short documentary video</li>
   </ul>
  </projects>
  <facultybios><strong>George Freeman</strong> is a clinical psychologist whose teaching interests
   include multicultural counseling, social psychology, social justice, human development, community
   psychology, environmental psychology, antibias studies, executive coaching and organizational
   systems development. He earned an M.A. and Ph.D. in clinical psychology from Southern Illinois
   University, and a B.A. in liberal arts, secondary education from Adams State
     University.<p><strong>Laura Citrin</strong>&#160;is a social psychologist with research and
    teaching interests in the psychology of emotions (particularly disgust), gender, the body, and
    moralizing processes. She earned an interdisciplinary Ph.D. in social psychology and
    women&#8217;s studies from the University of Michigan; an M.A. in social psychology from the
    University of Michigan; a B.S. in psychology from the University of Washington; and a B.A. in
    political science from the University of California, Berkeley.</p><p><strong>Heesoon
     Jun</strong> began teaching multicultural counseling at Evergreen in 1996 and has taught
    psychology ever since. A native of Seoul, South Korea, her bicultural and bilingual experiences
    are instrumental in teaching diversity, multiculturalism, social justice and equity. Her
    teaching interests include clinical, counseling, educational psychology, and human services. Her
    book <em>Social Justice, Multicultural Counseling, and Practice: Beyond a Conventional
     Approach</em>, was published in 2009. She holds a Ph.D. in educational psychology from the
    University of Washington, an M.A. in clinical psychology from Radford University, and a B.S. in
    psychology from Washington State University.</p><p><strong>Mukti Khanna</strong> is a practicing
    psychologist who incorporates mindfulness-based practices, expressive arts therapy, and
    psychotherapy into her practice. She has taught at conferences and groups both in the U.S. and
    abroad, including as an invited international guest faculty for the First Russian International
    Expressive Arts Festival in Moscow in 2012. Her teaching interests include multicultural
    studies, integrative health, medical qigong, human development, transpersonal, developmental and
    clinical psychology, expressive arts therapies, and consciousness studies. She earned a Ph.D. in
    clinical psychology from the University of Tennessee and a B.A. in human biology from Stanford
    University.</p><strong>Carrie Margolin&#8217;s</strong> expertise is in cognitive psychology.
   Her teaching and research interests include experimental psychology, cognitive science, animal
   language, attention, eyewitness testimony, research design and methodology, statistics, cultural
   studies, Jewish studies, gay and lesbian studies, and gender. In 2009, she received the Western
   Psychological Association&#8217;s Outstanding Service Award. She earned a Ph.D. in experimental
   psychology from Dartmouth College and a B.A. in social science at Hofstra
   University.</facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/visual-media-arts</url>
  <title>Visual and Media Arts</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:06</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T11:40:46</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode/>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Sculpt as you learn about the chemistry of clay. Draw to study stream ecology.
    Produce a documentary film. Exhibit art pieces to the public.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement-1-2">
    <img alt="Rites of Passage art show" class="illus-full" src="images/rites-of-passage2.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">The studio open house for the Rites of Passage program.</p>
   </div>
   <p>Studying visual and media arts at Evergreen is different than attending an arts school. By
    setting your study within the context of an interdisciplinary liberal arts education, you will
    expand your skills in analytical thinking, critical reading, and writing as well as discover
    themes and ideas that support and refine your artistic practice.</p>
   <p>Our students apply the theoretical and critical concepts they are learning to a range of
    artistic practices, from solving design problems to the production of full-scale independent
    projects. You will not just learn to create art &#8212; you will learn to use artistic skills as
    a means for exploring the vast world of ideas.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world.</strong></p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Television Director" class="image-full"
     src="images/visual-media-arts/television-director.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Ready Camera One student Louie Armstrong directs a television interview in
     the <abbr title="Center for Creative &amp; Applied Media">CCAM</abbr> control room. See below
     for more information about the CCAM.</p>
   </div>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <div class="box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <div class="media media-alt">
     <div class="media-img">
      <a href="../about/alumni/audreymarrs.htm">
       <img alt="Audrey Marrs &#8217;96" src="images/profile_audrey.jpg"/>
      </a>
     </div>
     <div class="media-body">
      <p>On her first try at feature filmmaking, <a href="../about/alumni/audreymarrs.htm">Audrey
        Marrs '96</a> scored an Oscar nomination. On her second, she won.</p>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <p>Evergreen alumni artists routinely break new ground, creating original works that change the
    way we look at art&#8212;and the world. From making innovative textiles to reinterpreting
    traditional carving, photographing rock-n-roll to portraying Antarctica&#8217;s rarely seen
    environment, Greeners continue to add beauty and insight to the world around them.</p>
   <p>Others make it their business to nurture creative talent and bring it to the larger community.
    They are graphic designers, documentary film directors, animators and illustrators, fashion
    designers, photographers, clothiers, jewelers, carvers, and sculptors. Beyond making their
    careers directly in art, many Evergreen alumni are involved in the arts in other ways, either as
    artists outside of their jobs or in promotion, arts board leadership, or volunteering.</p>
   <p>The skills learned at Evergreen &#8212; visual and media literacy, presentation and
    communication, analytical and critical thinking &#8212; give students an advantage in their
    future work.</p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Nonfiction Media Production" class="image-full"
     src="images/visual-media-arts/nonfiction-media-production.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Greeners produced a program comprised of the short documentaries for the
     program Nonfiction Media: Sustainability and Justice in the television studio.</p>
   </div>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <div class="box caption-box supplement">
    <img alt="Student detailing a ceramic vase" class="image-full"
     src="images/visual-media-arts/summer-arts.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Addison Houston shapes a vase in the ceramics studio.</p>
   </div>
   <h3>Art Spaces</h3>
   <p>The art curriculum is supported by a wide range of studios and facilities for students to
    experience a variety of media.&#160;</p>
   <ul class="text-list">
    <li>Sculpture studios supporting stone- and wood-carving, plaster casting and assemblage are
     located close to the metal shop and wood shop for convenient access to equipment and tools</li>
    <li>3-D studios are equipped with tall ceilings, bright lighting and plenty of work space</li>
    <li>Two metals studios &#8212; one shop dedicated to large-scale, ferrous metal work including
     welding, cutting, and metal casting equipment, and a second fine metals studio for small-scale
     work with copper, brass, and silver, enameling and small-scale metal casting</li>
    <li>Newly renovated woodshop that includes tools and equipment to support sculpture and
     traditional wood crafts</li>
    <li>Newly renovated ceramics studio equipped with potter&#8217;s wheels, a slab roller, clay
     mixer, gas and electric kilns</li>
    <li>Spacious painting and drawing studios lit by both natural and electric light specifically
     designed for 2D media</li>
    <li>Non-toxic printmaking studio featuring etching, engraving, lithography, the largest
     typesetting collection in the state, silk-screen, wood- and lino-cut</li>
    <li>Photo studios (<a href="http://blogs.evergreen.edu/photoland">Photoland</a>) support
     photography in a variety of formats</li>
    <li>Digital Imaging Studio (DIS) is accessible to students interested computer-based imaging and
     production</li>
   </ul>
   <h3>Center for Creative and Applied Media (CCAM)</h3>
   <p>Evergreen offers advanced media access and education in a highly-current and technologically
    fluid environment. The <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/ccam/home.htm">CCAM</a> facilities
    include:</p>
   <ul class="text-list">
    <li>TV studio</li>
    <li>Production control</li>
    <li>Green room</li>
    <li>Sound effects studio</li>
    <li>Audio lab</li>
    <li>Small-scale studio</li>
    <li>Audio/video post-production</li>
    <li>5.1 Surround mix studio</li>
   </ul>
   <h3>Electronic Media</h3>
   <p><a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/electronicmedia">Electronic Media</a> provides technical
    media instruction and support for facilities that include:</p>
   <ul class="text-list">
    <li>Animation lab</li>
    <li>Audio studios</li>
    <li>Film editing suites</li>
    <li>Music technology labs</li>
    <li>Video and multimedia editing lab</li>
   </ul>
   <h3>Evergreen Art Gallery</h3>
   <p>Newly renovated <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/gallery">art gallery</a> features a cycle of
    provocative exhibits and installations by regional artists and touring exhibitions.</p>
   <h3>Media Loan</h3>
   <p>Students of all levels are welcome to borrow film, audio/video and photographic equipment from
     <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/medialoan">Media Loan</a>. You can learn how to use this
    equipment from our staff.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>Studio Projects: Outside the Lines</h3>
   <p>
    <em>
     <small>Offered Fall 2017&#8211;Winter 2018<br/>
     </small>
    </em>
   </p>
   <p>This program questions and explores the division between the purpose art has traditionally
    served and alternative ways art can operate. We will pursue this inquiry through multiple
    learning modes, including studio practice, contemporary art theory and art history lectures,
    screenings, readings, written assignments, individual creative projects, and seminars.</p>
   <p>We will ground the program in two studio practices: animation and printmaking. Because both
    originate in drawing, students will devote significant time to learning drawing skills and
    theory. Students will work back and forth between drawn and reproduced images, animation and
    intaglio printmaking, static and moving pictures. They will then develop independent projects
    that further their own inquiries into these practices. Creating individual and collective
    projects, students will gain basic studio skills and foundational visual and media literacy.
    They will learn a range of creative concept development practices, enhancing their knowledge of
    alternative ways of making and thinking about art.</p>
   <p>
    <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/studioprojectsoutsidethelines-16237"
     >View this program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
   <div class="box caption-box">
    <img alt="Drawing Marathon" class="illus-full"
     src="images/visual-media-arts/drawing-marathon.jpg"/>
    <p class="caption">Life drawing session in the Drawing Marathon intensive summer class with Shaw
     Osha.</p>
   </div>
  </sample>
  <projects/>
  <facultybios><strong>Evan Blackwell</strong> brings a range of artistic expertise and experience
   to the curriculum at Evergreen. His artistic practice attempts to draw order and harmony from
   otherwise chaotic urban environments. Evan's work often imposes elegant design principles onto
   found materials, scrap wood, manufactured materials, and hardware. His work links aesthetic value
   with sustainability, and proposes artistic practice and objects as avenues for seeking a personal
   relationship to urban living.<p><strong>Naima Lowe</strong> teaches experimental film and video.
    Her films, videos, performances, and writings have been seen at the Athens International Film
    and Video Festival, Ann Arbor Film Festival, Anthology Film Archive, The Knitting Factory, The
    Stella Elkins Tyler Gallery, The International Toy Theater Exhibition, and Judson Memorial
    Church. Her first film, "Birthmarks," was a Student Academy Awards Finalist, won Best
    Experimental Film at the Newark Black Film Festival, and was honored for Best Sound Design in
    the NextFrame International Student Film Festival. Her collaborative performance and
    installation "Mary and Sarah and You and Me" made its New York debut at the historic Judson
    Memorial Church.</p><p><strong>Lisa Sweet</strong> has taught at Evergreen since 1999. Her
    teaching has focused on the function and role of images and objects in the context of religious
    practices, early Christianity, and the Middle Ages. Her current artistic practice includes two-
    and three-dimensional works in oil painting, and printmaking in engraving and
   woodcut.</p></facultybios>
 </page>
 <page>
  <url>/studies/writing</url>
  <title>Writing</title>
  <created>2013-10-03T09:29:06</created>
  <changed>2016-10-06T11:51:41</changed>
  <lastmodifiedby>corradoi</lastmodifiedby>
  <metadescription/>
  <directorycode/>
  <intro>
   <p class="intro">Explore a range of genres from fiction, poetry, and screenwriting to creative
    nonfiction and science. Cultivate your ability to tell compelling stories. Translate human
    experience into artful literary work.&#160;</p>
   <p>
    <strong>
     <img alt="Art&#8211;Work" class="illus" src="images/art-work.jpg"/>
    </strong>
   </p>
   <p>At Evergreen, you'll work in small intensive groups with peers and faculty to refine your
    writing skills.</p>
   <p>Because of the interdisciplinary nature of our curriculum, you&#8217;ll have many
    opportunities to hone your craft, regardless of the genre in which you specialize.</p>
   <p>Evergreen faculty members have collaborated with students to produce written projects in
    numerous disciplines, including the book, <em>Defending Wild Washington: A Citizen&#8217;s
     Action Guide</em>, a collection of writing and art titled <em>Silk Roads Anthology: Identity
     and Travel</em>, and the bilingual anthology, <em>En Sus Propias Palabras/In Their Own
     Words</em>, which was distributed to libraries, schools, and community organizations serving
    Latino populations in Western Washington.</p>
   <p>Whether you want to become a novelist, a poet, a journalist, a copywriter, or any other type
    of writer, Evergreen will help you develop the techniques to become an effective communicator
    and artist of the written word.</p>
   <p>Join us in an education that doesn&#8217;t just <strong>change your life</strong> &#8212; it
    gives you the tools to <strong>change the world.</strong></p>
  </intro>
  <after>
   <div class="box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <div class="media media-alt">
     <div class="media-img">
      <a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/magazine/2013spring/until-were-free.htm">
       <img alt="Pat Thomas" src="images/profile-pat.jpg"/>
      </a>
     </div>
     <div class="media-body">
      <p><a href="http://www.evergreen.edu/magazine/2013spring/until-were-free.htm">Pat Thomas
        &#8217;12</a> published his first book while still a student.</p>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <p>Quality writing skills are a key asset to careers in any field requiring the ability to
    clearly convey information, ideas, and values. Studying writing at Evergreen prepares you for
    graduate studies and careers in media, publishing, business, nonprofit work, and academia. Many
    fields in creative writing require a college degree, including at least a bachelor&#8217;s and
    often an MFA in creative writing or an MA in literature, journalism, or a related field. Our
    alumni have an excellent record of success in graduate school. They also include numerous
    published authors, as well as professionals in law, education, publishing, marketing, and
    journalism.</p>
  </after>
  <resources>
   <h3>The Writing Center</h3>
   <p>As a writer, you may be able to work in our Writing Center to improve your own skills and
    share your knowledge and passion with others.</p>
   <h3>The Evergreen State College Press</h3>
   <p>Evergreen's newest media outlet annually publishes a small number of books showcasing
    exceptional student writing of high scholarly merit. Selections reflect the college&#8217;s
    intellectual and creative vitality and its innovative academic work. The press&#8217;s first
    release, <em>Writing American Cultures: Studies of Identity, Community, and Place</em>, which
    was published in 2013, features narrative nonfiction essays based on the ethnographic research
    of eight student authors.</p>
   <h3>Student Newspaper</h3>
   <p>Students interested in journalism, political commentary, and artistic critique produce
    evergreen&#8217;s student newspaper, the <em>Cooper Point Journal</em>.</p>
   <h3>Cross Cultural Poetics</h3>
   <p>This groundbreaking radio show, produced on campus at KAOS 89.3FM, introduces poets to
    listeners around the world.</p>
   <h3>Inkwell: The Student Guide to Writing at Evergreen</h3>
   <p>Produced by Writing Center tutors, <em>Inkwell</em> is used as a teaching tool. Its goal is to
    empower and inspire a wide range of audiences through the center's philosophies on writing,
    learning, and growth. <em>Inkwell</em> demonstrates a variety of styles from the traditional
    academic format to poetry-inducing prompts.</p>
   <h3>Vanishing Point</h3>
   <p>An online and print publication featuring art and writing of students and faculty,
     <em>Vanishing Point</em> is dedicated to showcasing the creative endeavors of Evergreen. With a
    commitment to accessibility to both artists and those who enjoy their work, <em>Vanishing
     Point</em> aims to cultivate the arts community and capture the artistic spirit of
    Evergreen.</p>
  </resources>
  <sample>
   <h3>Life as Literature: Studies in Literature, Interpretation, and Writing</h3>
   <div class="box pull-box supplement-alt-1-2">
    <p class="pull-quote">Quality writing skills are a key asset to careers in any field, where the
     ability to clearly and creatively express ideas and values is in high demand.</p>
   </div>
   <p>
    <em>
     <small>Offered Fall 2017</small>
    </em>
   </p>
   <p>The outsider philosopher Friedrich Nietzsche once confided in a letter that his only home was
    between the lines of his writing on the page.</p>
   <p>What does it mean to write yourself into being?</p>
   <p>This program will investigate the complex relationships between an author, the reader, and her
    pages: who or what speaks in a literary work? What emerges through a reader&#8217;s work of
    interpretation&#8212;a new work, a translation? This program&#8217;s goal is to help you become
    a more skillful and inventive interpreter, a better reader, and ultimately, a more adept writer.
    We will study and practice various methods of interpretation of literary texts, focusing on
    works of autobiography, self-portraiture, and self-creation as alter-ego. We will read poetic,
    dramatic, and narrative works as well as essays. Readings will include, among others, Martinican
    Aim&#233; C&#233;saire&#8217;s <em>Return to My Native Land</em>; <em>Illuminations</em> by
    Arthur Rimbaud; Emily Dickinson&#8217;s poems; Jean Genet&#8217;s <em>The Miracle of the
     Rose</em>; and Ana&#239;s Nin&#8217;s <em>Labyrinths</em>. Students will engage in study of
    interpretive methodologies, read critical essays in philosophical and psychological approaches
    to literature, and practice interpretive writing as well as creative exercises in writing
    themselves into being on the page. The program is preparatory for advanced study of world
    literature.</p>
   <p>
    <a
     href="http://www.evergreen.edu/catalog/2017-18/programs/lifeasliteraturestudiesinliteratureinterpretationandwriting-16447"
     >View this program in the catalog.</a>
   </p>
   <p>
    <img alt="Writing Power workshop" class="illus" src="images/writing-power-workshop.jpg"/>
   </p>
  </sample>
  <projects/>
  <facultybios>
   <p><strong>Steven Hendricks</strong> teaches creative writing, book arts and literature. His
    first novel, <em>Little is Left to Tell,</em> was published in 2014 by Starcherone Books. His
    writing can also be found in numerous journals and anthologies, including <em>Conjunctions</em>
    and <em>The Journal of Experimental Fiction.</em> His artist books have been widely exhibited in
    the United States and abroad. He obtained his MFA in Writing from The School of the Art
    Institute of Chicago and his BA from The Evergreen State College.</p>
   <p><strong>Miranda Mellis</strong> teaches fiction, nonfiction, and contemporary literature. She
    is the author of <em>The Quarry</em> (Trafficker Press, 2013), <em>The Spokes</em> (Solid
    Objects, 2012), <em>None of This Is Real</em> (Sidebrow Press, 2012), <em>Materialisms</em>
    (Portable Press at Yo-Yo Labs, 2009), and <em>The Revisionist</em> (Calamari Press, 2007). She
    holds an MFA in Literary Arts (Fiction) from Brown University and a BA in Writing and Literature
    from Naropa University.</p>
   <p><strong>Leonard Schwartz</strong> teaches poetry and literary arts. His critical interest lies
    in the intersection of poetry and philosophy. A poet and essayist, he produces and hosts the
    radio program, &#8220;Cross Cultural Poetics.&#8221; His most recent book is <em>If</em>
    (Talisman House, 2012). He is also the author of <em>At Element</em> (Talisman House, 2011),
     <em>A Message Back and Other Furors</em> (Chax Press, 2008), <em>The Library of Seven
     Readings</em> (Ugly Duckling Presse, 2008), and <em>Language as Responsibility</em> (Tinfish
    Editions, 2006). He obtained his MA in philosophy from Columbia University and his BA in Writing
    and Literature from Bard College.</p>
  </facultybios>
 </page>  <page>
    <title>aesthetics</title>
    <parentfield>Philosophy</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Philosophy</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>African American studies</title>
    <parentfield>cultural studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Cultural Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>agriculture</title>
    <intro><p>The colleges organic farm is at the center of agricultural learning on campus, helping you learn to grow food for yourself and others in the broader community, using ecologically informed methods of farming while also learning management and business skills appropriate for small-scale production. Youll focus on Northwest crop and livestock speciesincluding orchard fruit, potatoes, sheep, and poultryand be able to study chemistry, microbiology, and anatomy in a highly practical and experiential context.</p></intro>
    <parentfield>environmental studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Environmental Studies/Agriculture</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>American studies</title>
    <parentfield>history</parentfield>
    <directorycode>History</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>anthropology</title>
    <intro><p>As a multidisciplinary study of humans present and past, anthropology finds its way into many programs and courses. Youll find opportunities to think deeply about contemporary ways of life and to consider pre-modern and non-industrial human experiences. Anthropology faculty offer instruction and guidance in ethnographic fieldwork: approaches to listening, observing, documenting, and reflecting that will enable you to engage meaningfully with people and topics that matter to their communities. You will combine the study of anthropology with history, psychology, sociology, literature, religion, and biology in integrated and relevant ways.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Social Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>architecture</title>
    <parentfield>visual and media arts</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Visual Arts</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>art history</title>
    <parentfield>visual and media arts</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Visual Arts</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>astronomy</title>
    <parentfield>physics</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Mathematics and Physics</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>biochemistry</title>
    <parentfield>chemistry</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Chemistry</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>biology</title>
    <parentfield>biology and life sciences</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Biological Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>botany</title>
    <parentfield>biology and life sciences</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Biological Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>business and management</title>
    <parentfield>business, management, and entrepreneurship</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Business and Economics</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>classics</title>
    <intro><p>In classics, you study ancient Greek and Roman civilizations and the foundational works of European traditions of art, literature, science, and philosophy. You gain an understanding of past cultures and engage with ancient Greeks and Romans in a dialogue on perennial questions. The combination of classics and classical archaeology with other areas of study gives you the opportunity to explore the vitality of ancient works and their importance in modern times. Classical studies are commonly taught in concert with philosophy, political science, history, theatre, anthropology, visual arts, and natural sciences.</p>
</intro>
    <parentfield>history</parentfield>
    <directorycode>History</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>communication</title>
    <intro><p>Developing good communication skills is one of the fundamental goals of an Evergreen education. Writing and speaking are emphasized across the curriculum through multiple writing formats, small seminars, collaborative projects, and class presentations. In addition, if you wish to practice media-based communication skills, you have access to state-of-the-art sound recording and television studios, a thriving student-run newspaper, and an on-campus community radio station.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Literature, Language, and Communication</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>community studies</title>
    <intro><p>Evergreen has a rich legacy of working within communities on issues of treaty rights and sovereignty, economic and social justice, and a host of other issues. Working closely with faculty and various communities, youll learn a holistic approach to systemic change at the community level. As you learn to conduct community-based research (also known as participatory research, popular education, and action research), youll learn the history, philosophy, and modes of research vital to understanding the needs, challenges, and aims of specific communities.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Community Field-Based Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>consciousness studies</title>
    <parentfield>psychology</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Consciousness Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>cultural studies</title>
    <intro><p>Cultural studies is both its own unique field and an approach that cuts across the humanities and social sciences. Youll find programs and courses with an emphasis in African American studies, international studies, maritime studies queer studies, and womens and gender studies.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Cultural Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>dance</title>
    <parentfield>performing arts</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Performing Arts</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>ecology</title>
    <parentfield>environmental studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Environmental Studies/Agriculture</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>economics</title>
    <intro><p>Economics is taught across the curriculum. We apply economic theory to a broad array of issues, including poverty and economic inequality, public policy, alternatives to capitalism, environmental policy, corporate behavior, social equity, unemployment, area studies, and social movements. We emphasize economic history and inequality by race, class, and gender, and focus on multiple schools of economic theory from neoclassical and Keynesian theory to feminist economics and Marxist political economy. Youll have opportunities to study foundations of economic theory and their implications for economic policy, and the major debates among economists about such issues as the proper role of government and how to best end poverty and other problems.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Business and Economics</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>education</title>
    <intro><p>Evergreen is a great place to build a foundation for a career in education. Youll find programs and courses that explore national, state, and local school policies; cover theories about learning and cognitive development; observe and engage in classrooms; and learn strategies for working with second language learners. You will have opportunities to develop your content knowledge in specific teaching areas such as mathematics, English language arts, and the sciences, preparing you for application to a post-baccalaureate teacher certification program. Staff can provide you with guidance as you navigate the curriculum on your way to a successful and fulfilling teaching career.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Social Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>field studies</title>
    <intro><p>Evergreen provides many opportunities for in-depth learning through fieldwork. In social sciences such as psychology, sociology, or anthropology, you can learn to be a participant observer in the process of conducting ethnographic interviews. In the sciences, through extended time in the field you can learn to conduct field science in ecology at the advanced undergraduate level. Trips to local and remote locations provide the backdrop for independent and group research projects in a number of environmental studies fields.</p>
</intro>
    <parentfield>environmental studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Community Field-Based Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>gender and women&#039;s studies</title>
    <parentfield>cultural studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Cultural Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>geography</title>
    <intro><p>Learning geography typically focuses on interconnectionsbetween human beings and the natural environment, past and present, domestic and foreign realms, and rural and urban areasall at the different scales of our existence (from local to regional, national, and global). In geography-rich interdisciplinary programs, you'll learn about local places and the larger world humans inhabit, how they define their homelands, how they engage in conflict and cooperation with each other, and how they migrate. Youll have opportunities to study scholarly and imaginative works, develop skills in writing and research, and conduct policy research, fieldwork, and mapping.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Social Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>geology</title>
    <intro><p>Geology integrates a range of scientific disciplines to gain a comprehensive understanding of the Earth, the relationships between rocks, water, chemistry, biology, and the environment, in the context of a changing world. It is usually embedded in team-taught interdisciplinary programs that incorporate other science disciplines, as well as social sciences and arts. You can study geology at all levels; foundational physical geology is taught in lower levels; advanced study typically focuses on geochemistry and hydrogeology. Applied learning is emphasized, through field trips, field and lab observation, geographic information systems (GIS), and research projects. Youll develop quantitative reasoning, scientific literacy, and data analysis skills that prepare you to answer real-world questions.</p></intro>
    <parentfield>environmental studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Environmental Studies/Agriculture</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>government</title>
    <parentfield>political economy and political science</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Politics and Government</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>health</title>
    <parentfield>biology and life sciences</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Biological Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>hydrology</title>
    <parentfield>environmental studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Environmental Studies/Agriculture</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>international studies</title>
    <parentfield>cultural studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Cultural Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>language studies</title>
    <intro><p>You can begin or continue foreign language studies in an array of courses and programs. Our regular offerings include Spanish, French, Russian, German, Japanese, American Sign Language, and Chinese. In addition, Arabic, Basque, Irish Gaelic, Latin, and ancient Greek are taught from time to time. In full-time programs, both stateside and abroad, you can learn foreign languages through immersion in the cultures of the peoples who speak them. Common destinations include Argentina, Costa Rica, Japan, China, France, Italy, Greece, Turkey, and Egypt. In addition to foreign languages, Evergreen offers frequent opportunities in linguistics.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Literature, Language, and Communication</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>law and government policy</title>
    <parentfield>political economy and political science</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Politics and Government</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>law and public policy</title>
    <parentfield>political economy and political science</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Politics and Government</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>leadership studies</title>
    <parentfield>business, management, and entrepreneurship</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Business and Economics</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>linguistics</title>
    <parentfield>language studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Literature, Language, and Communication</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>literature</title>
    <intro><p>Literature is one of the pillars of a liberal education. By reading the imaginative prose and verse of authors from across the globe and through the centuries, we encounter humanity at its kindest and cruelest, in its hopes and fears, suffering and sublimity. You can study literature in combination with the arts, sciences, and social sciences, as well as in humanities-intensive programs and courses. Cultural studies and study-abroad opportunities typically feature a substantial literature component.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Literature, Language, and Communication</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>marine science</title>
    <parentfield>environmental studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Environmental Studies/Agriculture</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>maritime studies</title>
    <parentfield>cultural studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Cultural Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>mathematics</title>
    <intro><p>Mathematics is much more than working with numbers and solving equations. It underlies many daily decisions, is crucial to thinking critically about what we read and hear in the media, is the language of science and technology, and lies behind the games we play and the work we do. Mathematical and quantitative thinking is incorporated across the curriculum. Youll find it woven into programs and courses involving science, sociology, psychology, economics, linguistics, and the arts. We also offer opportunities to study mathematics as a discipline in its own right: both pure and applied and from beginning to advanced.</p></intro>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>media arts</title>
    <parentfield>visual and media arts</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Media and Film</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>media studies</title>
    <parentfield>visual and media arts</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Media and Film</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>moving image</title>
    <parentfield>visual and media arts</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Media and Film</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>music</title>
    <parentfield>performing arts</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Performing Arts</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>natural history</title>
    <parentfield>environmental studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Environmental Studies/Agriculture</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>outdoor leadership and education</title>
    <parentfield>education</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Social Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>philosophy</title>
    <intro><p>Philosophy can be studied in many programs and courses, allowing you to rigorously investigate claims about the grounds of existence, the possibilities for knowledge, the nature of justice, and the existence of Godto name a few. Faculty members have expertise in the theory of knowledge, ethics, aesthetics, the philosophy of science, linguistics, and the philosophy of religion. Both Eastern and Western ways of knowing are represented in our curriculum.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Philosophy</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>philosophy of science</title>
    <parentfield>philosophy</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Philosophy</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>physics</title>
    <intro><p>Our approach to physics and astronomy is experiential and hands-on. You work in small groups in labs and workshops to understand the laws and physical models describing interactions involving matter and energy. Physics is taught at all levels and with many other disciplines, including animation, music, sports, sustainability studies, and philosophy. If youre embarking on an academic pathway in the sciences, you can obtain a foundation in university-level physics that also include calculus and chemistry or computer science. At the advanced level, you can learn physics and astronomy in integrated programs that include applied mathematics and advanced physical chemistry.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Mathematics and Physics</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>physiology</title>
    <parentfield>biology and life sciences</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Biological Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>political economy</title>
    <intro><p>While studying political economy, you will learn the ways in which the U.S. and global economies have been organized and reorganized, how systems of economic and political power operate, and how they are changed. You can study the history of empires in structuring the global economy; examine food systems and agriculture; and mass medias role in social relationships. Youll learn how social change has occurred in the past so you can be a more effective agent of change. Finally, you can explore alternative visions for economies and societies that promote justice and environmental sustainability.</p>
</intro>
    <parentfield>political economy and political science</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Politics and Government</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>political science</title>
    <parentfield>political economy and political science</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Politics and Government</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>queer studies</title>
    <parentfield>cultural studies</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Cultural Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>religious studies</title>
    <parentfield>philosophy</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Philosophy</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>sociology</title>
    <intro><p>Sociology is the study of human social institutions and social relationships. You can explore the intricate and complex relationships of social structures in the context of real-life issues: gender, identity, poverty, communication, community, crime and criminal behavior, and more. Opportunities are available to apply quantitative and qualitative skills through research and internships.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Social Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>somatic studies</title>
    <intro><p>Somatic studies look at mind-body ways of knowing and living in the world and are guided by the assumption that cultivating body-based intelligence (<em>soma</em> in Greek) can be used to help individuals grow and change. This field of study offers opportunities to explore body-based literacy as it relates to leadership, communication, and engagement with social issues. You'll learn in many ways (academic, experiential, contemplative), using diverse modalities and multiple intelligences, studying somatics through body-centered approaches to mindfulness, movement workshops, creative expression, the arts, and academic work in psychology, health, and more.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Consciousness Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>study abroad</title>
    <intro><p>Each year, Evergreen students travel to more than 40 countries, and the college typically offers four or five interdisciplinary study abroad programs. These include studies in language, culture, field biology, and social justice. Another option involves student exchanges to partner universities in Japan, South Korea, and Denmark. Many students create their own study abroad opportunities through independent learning contracts and study abroad consortia. For more information, go to <a href="https://www.evergreen.edu/studyabroad">https://www.evergreen.edu/studyabroad</a>. </p>
</intro>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>sustainability studies</title>
    <intro><p>Sustainability isnt just a bandwagon were hopping onto. Its woven into the very fabric of our identity, and history, as an institution.  President Les Purce. Evergreen is dedicated to sustainability. This value is reflected in our curriculum as well as our operations. Many programs and courses focus on the concept of sustainability from an interdisciplinary perspective. Areas of study include sustainable development, environmental policies, ethics, ecology, landscape architecture, city and regional planning, economics, natural resources, sociology, and anthropology.</p></intro>
    <directorycode>Sustainability Studies</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>theater</title>
    <parentfield>performing arts</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Performing Arts</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>visual arts</title>
    <parentfield>visual and media arts</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Visual Arts</directorycode>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>zoology</title>
    <parentfield>biology and life sciences</parentfield>
    <directorycode>Biological Sciences</directorycode>
  </page>
</pages>